<string_table>
	<string id="st_sardina">
<text>Sardines "Pirate"</text>
</string>
<string id="st_sardina_descr">
<text>a Very tasty fish, caught in the Pacific ocean, and transported some stalkers to the exclusion zone. Shelf life 1.5 months.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_nuts_2">
<text>Bank with nuts "BIM BOM"</text>
</string>
<string id="st_nuts_2_descr">
<text>the Bank of nuts with increased amounts of vitamins. They can be quickly filled and a bit to regain energy.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_wild_drink">
<text>"Wild" beverage</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_wild_drink_descr">
<text>the Drink is called "Wild" because it contains alcohol. The drink contains 5% alcohol, and drugs, causing the release of adrenaline in the blood.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_olivki">
<text>Olives</text>
</string>
<string id="st_olivki_descr">
<text>Fresh jar of olives in the Area the other does not exist. A popular and very marketable stalkers, but perishable in the zone. Slightly reduces the impact of radiation on the body.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_cheese">
<text>Processed cheese "Yantar"</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_cheese_descr">
<text>Normal processed cheese with local underground plant. Despite the fact that preparing in the Area, nobody has poisoned.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_galet">
<text>Biscuits</text>
</string>
<string id="st_galet_descr">
<text>Quite nutritious, allowing long storage of the product, but they are not particularly satisfied.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_shokolad">
<text>the Chocolate "Alenka"</text>
</string>
<string id="st_shokolad_descr">
<text>a Favorite treat of many stalkers. An excellent remedy against bad mood.</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_batonchik">
<text>Chocolate</text>
</string>
<string id="st_batonchik_descr">
<text>Delicious bar of milk chocolate with cream filling. An excellent remedy against bad mood.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_beer">
<text>Beer "Zhigulevskoe"</text>
</string>
<string id="st_beer_descr">
<text>Good to drink, uplifting. Barely noticeable to reduce the effect of radiation on the body.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_juice">
<text>Orange juice "Default"</text>
</string>
<string id="st_juice_descr">
 <text>a Nutritional product, perfectly restoring health.</text>
</string>


<string id="TGZ_jerky">
<text>Beef</text>
</string>
<string id="TGZ_jerky_desc">
<text>Your favorite beef - perfectly seasoned and moderately salty , it will support your hand in a few hours. This single batch were collected from the best meat in the Area, so side effects are a little weaker than your typical Stalker diet .</text>
</string>
<string id="chips">
<text>Chips</text>
</string>
<string id="chips_descr">
 <text>Light potato chips. Good source of salt and preservatives . Useful thing in the Area.</text>
</string>
<string id="TGZ_hash">
<text>Biscuits with hashish</text>
</string>
<string id="TGZ_hash_desc">
<text>Eating them, you'll find that it's not so bad.</text>
</string>
<string id="TGZ_cpcb">
<text>Salty crackers</text>
</string>
<string id="TGZ_cpcb_desc">
<text>These crispy pieces are perfect go for Breakfast in the Area.</text>
</string>
</string_table>