<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>

	<string id="est_work">
		<text>Is there any work for me ?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="est">
		<text>Here's what I have.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_1">
		<text>Find artefact "Medusa"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_1_text">
		<text>There is someone from the Big Land who ordered a "Medusa". The work is easy and the reward is small. Deal ?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="otmena">
		<text>Well, no.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="vozm">
		<text>I'll take it.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="vip">
		<text>I'm here for the job.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="nagrada">
	<text>The job is done... Where's the reward ?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="prin_art">
		<text>Bring what's has been promised to the customer.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_2">
		<text>Find the artifact "Stone Flower"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_2_descr">
		<text>Find the artifact "Stone Flower", formed in the anomaly "Springboard". The pay for it should be good.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_2_text">
		<text>There is a demand for a "Stone Flower" artefact from some jewelers, maybe they want seduce some beautiful ladies, eh? You'll get it - I've got a fee and a bottle, to drink to their health...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_3">
		<text>Find the artifact "Night Star"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_3_descr">
		<text>Find the "Night Star" - a rare and expensive artifact.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_3_text">
		<text>There is one problem... Somehow unpleasant. It looks like the military are developing new gear. So, they came to order a "Night Star" - is a rare artifact that can reduce the weight carried... So you're taking the job ? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_4">
		<text>Find a "Meat chunk" artefact</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_4_descr">
		<text>Find the artifact "Meat Chunk", formed in chemical anomalies</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_4_text">
		<text>There is an order for an artifact, you need one effective against chemistry, called "Meat Chunk"! They have a kind of laboratory. You'll get there with the artefact and you will get the money yourself and help people.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_find_artefact_1_descr">
		<text>Find the artifact "Medusa", formed in the anomaly "Springboard".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="otmena_1">
		<text>These tasks are not interesting to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="return_for_reward">
		<text>Come back for the reward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="return_for_reward_bring">
		<text>Bring what's has been promised to the customer.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_monster_part_1">
		<text>Bring a Bloodsucker's Jaw</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_monster_part_1_descr">
		<text>The blood-sucking tooth attracts good luck? Let's see if the bloodsucker is lucky</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_monster_part_1_text">
		<text>I heard the belief that the blood-sucking tooth attracts good luck? It would be like if someone who wears such a tooth on his neck, anomalies are released, and the artifacts themselves go into their hands? In general, this is all garbage, but there are fools who believe and are willing to pay good money. Bring the jaws of the bloodsucker, I'll pay you well.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_monster_part_2">
		<text>Bring a tail of pseudo dog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_monster_part_2_descr">
		<text>Bring a tail of pseudo dog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_monster_part_2_text">
		<text>Winter is coming soon. And what about winter there, on the big earth, women like to wear? Correctly! Furs they like to wear. So the fashion has gone new, from the tails of pseudo dogs accessories do all kinds of things. Wool there is some kind of special! In short, there is an order for such a tail. Will you take it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_1">
		<text>Kill the bandit leader</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_1_descr">
		<text>Kill the leader of the bandits who crossed the road to the merchant. Most likely, he will not be alone, but with protection... The work is complicated, but they also pay adequately.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_1_text">
		<text>You'll have to finish off one handsome man - he's one of the bandits. Recently, the bandits, by his order, intercepted my courier and gutted it to zero, and with those who touched my people, the conversation was short... In general, I will not stay in Duty. So how do you take?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_2">
		<text>Kill the stalker-huckster</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_2_descr">
		<text>Kill a stalker... Yes, not the best job of all - to raise a hand on a colleague. However, they pay well, and, perhaps, this is the main thing?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_2_text">
		<text>I had some disagreements with a single merchant. Well, he does not want to work with me, and hell with him! Only rumors will not be allowed to dismiss rascals. In general, it is necessary to finish with him, so that others do not dissolve. To know who is the boss...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_3">
		<text>Kill the novice stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_3_descr">
		<text>Finish a novice stalker, who may not be a beginner at all... Who then? However, the devil take care of them! The main thing is that the job is dust-free.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_3_text">
		<text>There is one here, everything is spinning, he mows down to the beginner, but only a strange one... In general, if he disappears unnoticed, it will be a good favor for me. Do you understand what I mean?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_4">
		<text>Kill a stalker nicknamed Demon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_4_descr">
		<text>Eliminate one of the trading competitors of the trader Sidorovich - a stalker nicknamed Demon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_4_text">
		<text>Demon, he's Oleg Gusarov... The former commander. Until I got into other people's business, I had no complaints against him - a loner is a loner. Only recently, sthere have been some complains. And now this is a serious problem, and it must be solved quickly. Do you take the order?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_5">
		<text>Kill Father Diodorus</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_5_descr">
		<text>To kill a man preaching in the Zone against the extraction of artifacts and trade with them? Exactly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_5_text">
		<text>I always said: business and religion are two parallel occupations, they can not be crossed closely, and in each other's affairs, no-one! Only to this father, God forgive Avid... Hmmm... Well, he can not understand this simple truth. Everything is delirious, that the gathering of artifacts, and especially the trade in them seduces the way of sinful people not only in the Zone, but all over the world - well, everything in that spirit. He, you know, calls in general to destroy artifacts - ah ?! You can only imagine how he thought of it! The worst thing, some of them are being started on nonsense. I to this Avid on some goat did not come, and he knows his own oppression. The deal is this: you send it upstairs to an audience... Understood, right? And I give you artifact some solid. So, on hands?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_6">
		<text>Kill the "sales representative"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_6_descr">
		<text>Kill the "sales representative". The trader monitors his reputation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_kill_stalker_6_text">
		<text>Think about it, there is an oddball circling nearby, which is represented by my sales representative, uses my reputation, and then pushes it out! Broken trunks, crumbling armor, overdue canned food... I already had a couple of showdowns with the discontented. In short, I need a person who will talk with the "sales representative". Up to the substandard.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="kill_stalker">
		<text>Kill the target.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sim_stalker_veteran_gusarov_name">
		<text>Oleg "The Demon" Gusarov</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sim_stalker_master_diador_name">
		<text>Father Avid</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_1">
		<text>Find the artifact "Meat Chunk"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_1_descr">
		<text>Get the "Meat Chunk" - an artifact, giving protection from chemical anomalies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_1_text">
		<text>Here recently, some scientists came in, they left the order for the "Hunk of meat". You know, they have an interest in this chemical artifact ! Hmm... So you're taking? In principle, do not force.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_2">
		<text>Find the artifact "Crystal Thorn"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_2_descr">
		<text>Find the artifact "Crystal Thorn", which helps the wearer get rid of radiation.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_2_text">
		<text>"Stinky"? No, not that. "Crystal Vodichka"? No, not back then... Ugh! "Crystal thorn," oh how! So, look: ordered me an artifact "Crystal Thorn". You know this? It seems as if you have it, then the radiation will calmly bring it out. Well, what can you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_3">
		<text>Find the artifact "Night Star"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_3_descr">
		<text>Find the artifact "Night Star" - to help the domestic military science.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_3_text">
		<text>Need an artifact "Night Star". Unfortunately, he does not fulfill wishes - he is checked, but he can even enrich himself. Scientists for him give good money. Something, they say, is wrought on the basis of the military... Well, so what?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_4">
		<text>Find the artifact "Flash"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_4_descr">
		<text>Find the artifact "Flash"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_4_text">
		<text>The task is simple, but the payment is good. You need to find the artifact "Flash". Do not even ask who ordered what for. You take?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_5">
		<text>Find the artifact "Goldfish"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_5_descr">
		<text>Find the artifact "Goldfish"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_find_artefact_5_text">
		<text>Labeled, do you know the tale of the Golden Fish? In, in! A lot of jokes about her. So, there is an old man who wants to catch her. In general, we need a unique artifact "Goldfish", the customer is external, solid. Will you help?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_1">
		<text>Kill a serviceman</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_1_descr">
		<text>We must finish off an unknown serviceman. The work seems to be pretty simple... it's strange that this is an order for a person in uniform, and the customer is clearly very angry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_1_text">
		<text>I need you to deal with one military... and do not ask who he is, and it gave me no reason! Just do it. Well? Can I rely on you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_2">
		<text>Kill the stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_2_descr">
		<text>Finish one of the stalkers. Death to the deceiver - such is the revenge of the merchant.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_2_text">
		<text>You know, there are people about whom you can never say anything bad... believe them, right? You rely like on yourself... But suddenly you suddenly find out that this is some kind of so cunning and deceitful son of a bitch that... In general, there is a serious matter: you have to get even with one type. Do it, and the rest follows me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_3">
		<text>Kill the stalker from "Monolith" faction</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_3_descr">
		<text>Find a former trader's friend and help him die.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_3_text">
		<text>Once I had a friend... I can not believe it, right? Eh... And in fact we with it together in the Zone have come, when here it still in sight was not. And that's all we did, wherever we climbed... Yes, the young ones were, the sea was knee-deep... Only it was always not enough for him. He wanted to go to the center of the Zone, and he pulled me, and I refused - and rightly so, he refused... We posbachilsya then great, and he left... Only they tell me, saw him there... he is for "Monolith" now is standing. So you're here, Labeled... As a man I ask - find him, and... in general, so that he does not suffer, after all, I suppose... He was like a brother to me, you know?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_4">
		<text>Kill a stalker nicknamed Ghoul</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_4_descr">
		<text>Find and kill the stalker, known under the nickname Ghoul.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_4_text">
		<text>Everything, this type has got me! I'm talking about Vampire; You know him, no? Uh, you bastard! He's not sucking blood from people, but luck. Whoever goes - everyone will be covered alone, he is alive and well! Fifth time already! In short, there is something unclean here. There is a big desire to put flowers on the grave of this Ghoul... Well, you like, agree?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_5">
		<text>Kill the stalker, nicknamed Sparrow</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_5_descr">
		<text>Find Sparrow and avenge the death of another stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_kill_stalker_5_text">
		<text>Nobles, damn! Pushkin with Lermontov! .. And so, boobies, under anomalies and bullets go every day, so also dueling in fashion took! No, well, you just think about it: there was a dispute here... Nobody remembers it already, for what reason. Only they decided to let the two dudes go. Well, here you are: one took and died... What a stalker was! and the second - Sparrow's name - quickly knocked over, because I myself would have sent him a bullet into the intestines at the first case. Find him. I'm sure he has not managed to get out of the Zone yet. Doing it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_monster_part_1">
		<text>Get a "flesh" eye</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_monster_part_1_descr">
		<text>Get the eye of a "flesh"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_monster_part_1_text">
		<text>Soon we have a holiday, and there will be a festive dinner, and some local gourmets in a particularly upbeat mood (we will not point the finger) will definitely want to try my crown dish - the eyes of the "flesh" under the pork sauce. That is, in its own juice under mayonnaise. In general, we need the eye of this creature, and soon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_monster_part_2">
		<text>Bring boar hoof</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_monster_part_2_descr">
		<text>Bring boar hoof</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barmen_monster_part_2_text">
		<text>Do you know that we prepare horns and hooves? This is now very rare. From local mutated hoofs make excellent jewelry, I know one jeweler, he is interested. So go ahead, find a boar hoof, and money'll be in your pocket.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_kill_stalker_1">
		<text>Neutralize the bandit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_kill_stalker_1_descr">
		<text>Neutralize the bandit Pig.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_kill_stalker_1_text">
		<text>The name of the object is Kocherga. One of the most brutal leaders of bandits, a bastard and a rapist... His head is clearly not right: they say that in the Zone some rare disease has earned. Now he has quite often complete failures in memory, and when he comes to himself, he does not remember where he is or who. Nevertheless, it is always armed and very aggressive. Presumptive location: Dark valley. Ready for the assignment?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_1">
		<text>Bring the "Fireball" artifact</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_1_descr">
		<text>Get the artifact "Fireball" for research.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_1_text">
		<text>We managed to get an artifact in the laboratory! This is a breakthrough! Now the whole world will hear about our successes. And there the Nobel Prize is just around the corner! This is a unique artifact - "Film", its main quality - protection from chemical burns. Do you want me to give it to you on behalf of science? However, one request - in return I need an artifact "Fireball", you know this? The unique thermal properties of its surface require detailed study.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_2">
		<text>Find the artifact "Gravy"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_2_descr">
		<text>Deliver the artifact "Gravi" in the hands of scientists.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_2_text">
		<text>We came close to understanding the nature of gravity, in fact, very soon we will be able to create a new generation of engines on an antigravitational basis, and, quite possibly, we will open the road to the stars. For this we need the "Gravy" artifact, and quickly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_3">
		<text>Get the artifact "Medusa"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_3_descr">
		<text>Artifact "Medusa" is needed by scientists for research in the field of space-time. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_3_text">
		<text>Our research complex is on the verge of discovering the secret of space-time. The possibility of teleportation is not fantastic! "Funnel" is an anomaly that squeezes space, and not just gravitationally affects objects, as some of my stagnant opponents-theorists think, who sit in warm research institutes, zealously chewing chalk. They will sweat glasses when they find out what kind of results science can achieve in the field! Get me the "Medusa" artifact, please.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_4">
		<text>Get the artifact "Moonlight"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_4_descr">
		<text>To provide scientists on Yantar with "Moonlight". A good artifact...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_4_text">
		<text>We urgently need materials to continue research in the field of energy. You see, we learned how to generate electricity with artifacts. True, while the efficiency is not high enough. The best results we have achieved with the artifact "Moonlight". Bring us a sample for further experiments.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_5">
		<text>Get the artifact "Sea Hedgehog"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_5_descr">
		<text>Scientists to improve costumes need an artifact "Sea Hedgehog."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_find_artefact_5_text">
		<text>You probably know that our costumes have the best protection against radiation. The secret is that we impregnate them with essences from a special, rather rare, artifact. To produce the next batch of costumes, we need such an artifact, you call it "Sea Hedgehog."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_1">
		<text>Bring part of a snork</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_1_descr">
		<text>Get a snork part in these places should not be a problem.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_1_text">
		<text>We met Semenov when I was giving lectures on genetics at the university, and he was my student. So I became his scientific adviser. Then we just opened the veil of the mystery of modifying the genome. What am I talking about? Oh yes. For genetic studies, we need samples of fresh cells of the muscular tissue of a snorkel. For genetic material you will have to go to the marshes. There is a hypothesis that snorkel as a species is a new stage of human development. To know for sure, you need a DNA test!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_2">
		<text>Get a flesh eye</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_2_descr">
		<text>Just in case, it's worth keeping your body away from eggheads! And the eye of the flesh, so be it, I'll get it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_2_text">
		<text>Good news, young man: we have a very interesting job for you! I think you, as a thinking person with sufficient life experience, appreciate the revolutionary nature of the ideas of my colleagues. The fact is that research has shown: the eyes of beings, called in common parlance "flesh", are supplied - do you listen carefully? - Olfactory receptors! Thus, they not only see with their eyes, but also smell them! We are preparing for an operation to transplant this wonder-eye to one of... Our volunteer assistants. I think we are waiting for a real sensation! But we need a donor body. Will you help us?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_3">
		<text>Get a boar leg</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_3_descr">
		<text>Bring the boar to the ham scientist. In principle, they will manage the hoof.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_3_text">
		<text>I greet you... Uh... Wanderer! I'm glad that you decided to visit us: we just need a person to participate in a very important experiment. Colleague Benter wants to try to make something edible from the local fauna for a practical experiment to investigate the effect of mutated protein on human organisms. While we decided to stay on the boars. We need a ham. Boar's leg, you understand? If you take this case, I beg you, choose the individual more fat.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_4">
		<text>Find a pseudo dog tail</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_4_descr">
		<text>Provide scientists with tail pseudo dogs for their strange experiments.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_4_text">
		<text>Hello colleague! We still can not unravel the mechanism observed by the pseudo-dog of amazing properties, so we decided to change the vector of our searches. This time we'll start from the end... Why are you smiling? What do you... Ah, yes. I think I understand. You see, young man, we need the tail of this creature, located at the end... Yes, at the end of the body. It was not about the reproductive organs of this mammal! Behind them, you may have to take a walk next time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_5">
		<text>Get a bloodsucker jaw</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_5_descr">
		<text>What they are going to do with the jaws of the bloodsucker - I do not care. It is important to me how much they will give for this rarity.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_monster_part_5_text">
		<text>Oh, stalker, glad to see you! Listen... Have you already encountered bloodsuckers in your travels? If not, we would like it to happen. As soon as you can, bring us the lower jaw of a representative of this species - and with all, so to speak, cutlery. Unfortunately, I can not dedicate you to the details of the experiment... Perhaps this will negatively affect the stability of your psyche. We'll wait.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_ecolog_job_complete">
		<text>You did a great job! Let me give you a reward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_1_descr">
		<text>Kill the "Duty" security chief, trying to do it as quietly as possible.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_1_text">
		<text>It would be nice if the security chief of "Duty" quietly disappeared. Then they will have a small mess, and I will be able to introduce several guys into their grouping. And then, and the devil is not joking... Okay, I will not roll my lip ahead of time. I advise you to work the client from afar and quietly, without making a fuss.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_2">
		<text>Kill Captain Ivantsov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_2_descr">
		<text>Kill the close assistant leader of "Duty" - Captain Ivantsov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_2_text">
		<text>The task is difficult, I warn you right away, but it's worth it. It is necessary to punish Ivantsov - there is such a henchman in the commander of "Duty". He is engaged in the most dirty work: punitive campaigns, raids... You would know how many of our guys he vzdernul! It's time to deal with this rubbish finally. If you decide, I advise you first of all to arm yourself well.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_3">
		<text>Kill Colonel Petrenko</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_3_descr">
		<text>Kill Colonel Petrenko - one of the founding fathers of the group "Duty".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_3_text">
		<text>Colonel Petrenko... I do not know if you heard this name, met him or not, but it's good to meet you. This man is one of the founders of "Duty" and one of the most terrible of our enemies. Make sure your conversation ends sooner... for him. Will you pull it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_4">
		<text>Kill the neutral-stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_4_descr">
		<text>Find and destroy the neutral-stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_4_text">
		<text>A peasant is one, he's walking around here. So he threw such a thing, he shot our gun once. And such forgiveness can not be. You take the case? We will pay, do not worry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_5">
		<text>Kill one of the "Duty" commanders</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_5_descr">
		<text>Kill one of the "Duty" commanders</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_5_text">
		<text>I pay for the head of any of the heads of "Duty"! If you fill up, return for the reward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_6">
		<text>Kill a stalker nicknamed Scarecrow</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_6_descr">
		<text>Kill the stalker, nicknamed Scarecrow.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_6_text">
		<text>We destroy monsters, only for us it is a matter of survival, not profit. Populations of mutants are not so numerous; moreover, they are also living beings, so we can not allow their complete destruction. Some individuals do not understand this. A good example: there is one stalker, Scarecrow is called. He got his nickname for a reason, but because he pricked up the rummaging of stuffed animals for selling them. We warned him, only to no avail. Will you do a good deed for Mother Earth?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_7">
		<text>Kill the stalker, nicknamed Barin.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_7_descr">
		<text>Kill the stalker, nicknamed Barin - the main intendant of the group "Duty".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_kill_stalker_7_text">
		<text>Ham, a sycophant, a hypocrite, a coward... He's a stalker, Barin. As you see, a man of remarkable spiritual qualities, which helped him to get into the upper echelons of the "Duty". Now he is engaged in providing supplies and food to the group, although from time to time he is still involved in raids. It is necessary to get rid of it - especially since almost all the connections of the "Duty" in the sense of supply are tied to Barin.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_monster_part_1">
		<text>Bring a boar leg</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_monster_part_1_descr">
		<text>Bring a boar leg</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_monster_part_1_text">
		<text>We have a festive dinner planned for Bob Marley's birthday. You, brother, get us a boar leg more delicious, eh? Or two! Jah will not forget you!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mercenary_kill_stalker">
		<text>Kill the master stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mercenary_kill_stalker_descr">
	<text>For the murder of every master, a mercenary is ready to pay well. the fewer masters, the easier it is for mercenaries.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mercenary_kill_stalker_text">
		<text>For the murder of every master, a mercenary is ready to pay well. The fewer masters, the easier it is for mercenaries.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tm_freedom_job_complete">
		<text>Well, young man, young man! Work for five - keep earned.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="kocherga">
		<text>Poker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="agr_ratcatcher">
		<text>Deserter</text>
	</string>
	<string id="upir">
		<text>Ghoul</text>
	</string>
	<string id="vorobey">
		<text>Sparrow</text>
	</string>
	<string id="chuchelo">
		<text>Scarecrow</text>
	</string>
	<string id="master">
		<text>Master</text>
	</string>
</string_table>