<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_trader_ashot_start_dialog_0">
		<text>What can I sell you today?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_b19_freedom_yar_start_dialog_0">
		<text>Hello, stalker. What do you need?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_b220_trapper_start_11">
		<text>I'm Trapper... There's no need to introduce yourself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_b220_trapper_start_12">
		<text>What brings you here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_medik_start_dialog_0">
		<text>You looking for medical supplies, or just here for a chat?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_medik_need_health_care_0">
		<text>I need medical assistance.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_medik_need_health_care_1">
		<text>Let's have a look...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_medik_need_health_care_2">
		<text>Let's have a look... Well, your liver is bigger than I'd expect, but that's an occupational hazard, right? Apart from that, you're as healthy as a burer.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_medik_need_health_care_11">
		<text>[continue...]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_medik_need_health_care_111">
		<text>That's better.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_start_dialog_11">
		<text>So, what have you got to say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_start_dialog_12">
		<text>What's your business here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_0">
		<text>Tell me about Freedom.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_1">
		<text>It's a long story. What do you want to know?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_1111">
		<text>What is it that you do here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_11111">
		<text>We're making sure that various officials don't conceal anything from the common folk. You know how it is: as soon as they find a new lab or some documents that shed light on the secrets of the Zone, they immediately organize a military operation and clean everything up better than a friggin' hoover. The only way of finding shit out is by getting there first.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_1112">
		<text>What brought you to the center of the Zone?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_11121">
		<text>Well, the boys felt like taking a stroll in a new place... Just kidding. It's an opportunity to find stuff that the world ain't seen before. Neither the army nor stalkers have been here before, so there's something new everywhere you look.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_111211">
		<text>Did you find anything?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_1112111">
		<text>A couple of locked doors and some weird new artefacts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_1113">
		<text>How did you end up in Freedom?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_11131">
		<text>Well, I was friends with Freedom leaders back when there was no Zone. Mind you, in those days, they weren't leaders: they were regular hippies. So, when I made a move into the Zone in search of artefacts and ran into familiar faces, I figured I might as well go with what I know.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_1114">
		<text>What do you think about Duty?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_11141">
		<text>They're idiots, that's what I think. I mean, why the hell would they want to destroy the Zone? It's not consuming precious resources or getting bigger... or anything. They could just sit there and study it to their heart's content. Just think of how many scientific discoveries could be made... I mean, in the history of man-kind, no one has never been able to understand anti-gravitation, right? And in the Zone,  you've got ready-made anti-gravitation devices lying all over the place. It wouldn't hurt to kick their asses out of here, but it's too much hassle. By the way, don't be confused by our relations here at Yanov. We are at war... it's just that Yanov has been made neutral territory, if you know what I mean.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_1115">
		<text>Okay. Forget about it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_freedom_leader_about_you_11151">
		<text>No problem.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_barmen_start_dialog_11">
		<text>Welcome to my humble abode of pleasure and joy. You after joy, pleasure, or both in equal measure?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_barmen_start_dialog_12">
		<text>You come to chill? My drinks ain't nothing special, but this is a welcoming and friendly place!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_barmen_start_dialog_13">
		<text>I got all the shit you're ever gonna need. What are you after? You fancy some chow, a drink, or feel like firing off a few rounds?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="jup_b6_scientist_nuclear_physicist_start_11">
		<text>What would you like to say to me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_b16_biochemist_oasis_start_11">
		<text>What brings you here?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="jup_b6_scientist_medic_start_11">
		<text>What brings you here?</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Ashot and Yar -->
	<string id="st_jup_yar_reply_1">
		<text>You go tell %s to get his fat ass over here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_yar_reply_2">
		<text>Doesn't he know I'm busy? Tell him to come over here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_yar_reply_3">
		<text>I don't get paid for walking. Tell him to come to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_yar_reply_4">
		<text>What? Does he want a wheelchair? Go fetch %s for me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_yar_reply_5">
		<text>Where is %s? I can't fix it until he brings it here.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_jup_ashot_reply_1">
		<text>If %s wants it, tell him to come over here and take it from me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_ashot_reply_2">
		<text>Come again? If he wants it, he comes and gets it. Okay?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_ashot_reply_3">
		<text>You tell that balding bastard to drag himself over here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_ashot_reply_4">
		<text>I cannot leave my shop alone. He's gotta come to me, eh?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_ashot_reply_5">
		<text>Do I look like an errand boy? Tell %s to get it himself.</text>
	</string>

<string id="rabi_0">
		<text>Are you a local trader?</text>
	</string>

<string id="rabi_1">
		<text>Something like that. Rabinovich calls me. Ya read here from the second explosion at the nuclear power plant. It was then that I started my career as a seller. If you need trunks, this is for me. And for the most sophisticated buyers, I have some "exclusive" types of armor. Although, we must admit, among this rabble, it is more and more difficult to conduct business. Because of the Fagot's hunters, it is increasingly difficult for my "main" clients to take goods from me. But before here there was silence and the smooth surface and not some fucking stalkers. The bubbles were streaming Simply. But times are changing, nothing can be done. Although there is a me One idea is left ... hehe ...</text>
	</string>

<string id="zver_info_0">
		<text>Can I ask you a few questions ?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zver_info_1">
		<text>Ask...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zver_info_1111">
		<text>What do you think about Rabinovich?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zver_info_11111">
		<text>And the fact that it is not as simple as it seems. I would not advise you to trust him. He was on Yanovo even before we came here with the rest of the hunters. According to rumors, he is dealing with monoliths who sat in the warehouse of containers, here on Jupiter. Do they even supply weapons to something else... Even I do not know... We almost every day shoot back from these rotten fanatics and this padla in the quiet pushes them with equipment... Misery... The problem is that the real we do not have any evidence of his '' bargains ''. But remember my word, as soon as this reptile misfires we show m to him "kuzkin mother"!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zver_info_1112">
		<text>Tell me about your group of hunters.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zver_info_11121">
		<text>We are engaged in the destruction of mutants and other evil spirits for a moderate fee. I even before coming to the Zone liked to go on a weekend shoot to shoot the animals. The living creatures of course are not a couple here, but still... Upon arrival in the ChZO, I experienced all the hardships of life here . Everything turned upside down. Then the animals rule the ball and not the people. It's not good... So I decided to change the balance of power, so to speak, and began hunting for the local fauna. Gradually I found my like-minded people and we organized a whole group of hunters on creatures of the zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zver_info_1113">
		<text>What can you tell us about Jupiter's surroundings?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zver_info_11131">
		<text>I'll tell you a damn place for you. Not for the weak in spirit. This area is just teeming with mutants and monoliths, fanatics even organized here a few base camps, they try to get us out of here, only they'll get a fuck out of them. Near scientists there are scientists, they have a whole the bunker that the military on the turntables dropped twenty days ago.Oh and the noise was. To the west is the village of Kopachi. There are wonders, there zombies roam... Humm... And in the east - Cement plant. There they say you can find tools for technicians, only no one has so far decided to go there t.V side of an old factory Jupiter walking strongly advise there any strange things tvoryatsya.Stalkery day and night bormochat that there poltergeists and other herobury navalom.Vot such things here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zver_info_1114">
		<text>What can you say about Gonta, Crab and Garmat?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zver_info_11141">
		<text>One of the best of my hunters. Gonta is an excellent shooter and friend, Crab is engaged in receiving orders for the destruction of mutants, so if you need work - to him to address. And about Garmata - he is one of the best technicians in these parts, repairs almost everything . He really has problems with tools like now, but it's as they say, business is everyday.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zver_info_1115">
		<text>Ah, okay. Have passed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zver_info_11151">
		<text>You know better.</text>
	</string>


<string id="gonta_0">
		<text>Tell me about hunting for mutants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_1">
		<text>I can tell only about schooling animals. Flesh and wild boars, blind dogs and pseudo dogs, snorkels, tuscans ... In principle, I can tell you about bloodsuckers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_1111">
		<text>Tell me about boars and flesh.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_11111">
		<text>Well, flesh is the most harmless of mutants. Try to stay away from stalkers, but will defend themselves if they attack. It is more dangerous if a wild boar is caught among the flesh. A three-hundred-kilogram beast is not your toy. Try not to be on the runway during the hunt... Use inertia. You understand, such a carcass can not turn around instantly. Dodge it - and shot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_1112">
		<text>Tell me about the blind dogs and pseudo dogs.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b106_stalker_gonta_about_mutants_11121">
		<text>Not as dangerous alone, as in a tightly flocked pack. Attacked only when hungry, but hungry almost always. If you are hunting a pack - try to beat from the hill, otherwise you will simply be dashed. Especially, if in a flock there are hard-nosed pseudo dogs. They are not many tenacious blind dogs, but much more cunning and dangerous. If in place of one whole flock suddenly appears, remember: those that attack you are phantoms. A real pseudo dog will stay away, only occasionally running up to bite... Try to figure it out. As soon as the real one dies, the phantoms dissolve.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_1113">
		<text>Tell me about snorks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_11131">
		<text>The remains of a man... One snork is a small danger for a snappy hunter. You wait, when he jumps on you, and in the air you thrust into him the charge of fraction. Worse, when there are several... Then you just have to beat them with all possible speed, dodging jumps. They know this, and prefer not to attack one by one.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_1114">
		<text>Tell me about the tushkanos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_11141">
		<text>The horror of a hunter... The most stupid thing to do is to underestimate them because of their small size. They are insanely fast, brisk and always - schooling animals. When dozens of small fangs tear you to pieces - in a moment you stop to underestimate, and you start to shoot. And then you understand the most terrible thing - it's very difficult for them to get there. Therefore, I advise all stalkers to always carry a loaded shotgun with them...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_1115">
		<text>Tell me about the bloodsuckers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_11151">
		<text>Almost ideal hunters with beautiful camouflage. When they are masked - they are almost invisible. If you go to the bloodsucker - try to frighten him. In motion, it can be seen. Remember - the bloodsucker tries to go to the victim from behind, braiding her scruff with his tentacles. Damn, an abomination... If you're not lucky, and ran into a few bloodsuckers - always control who is behind you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_1116">
		<text>Nevermind.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
