<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="isg_history_1">
<text>
They say there is one group of friends... when Their shamans are called, and when the druids. They say, even electronic equipment are not to nature, they say, closer and all that... Well, they say that the Zone on electronics... all sorts of electromagnetic radiation is stronger, reacts... Yes, and monsters at you to bring. As in their language, so the Area is a living organism. They say you can't go into it with the devices is the right man, and without any unnecessary portions cope. However, the machines they bring, goats, hauling... There would be teeth and claws to try... on the other hand, killed them in a Zone like not so much. No more us, they stick together fins... So it might be correctly guessed... They are, however, more like the Belarusian side in the Area go... And then it would be good for them to see... Yes checking along with how much they have artifacts in the usual pockets...</text>
</string>
<string id="isg_history_2">
 <text>you Know, what do you say? In this part, the sleeping Area is almost impossible... Me I am lucky, I can not sleep... and the people of those nightmares happen, that happen, and do not Wake up in the morning... of a broken heart, for example... Who the horses are driven, and who tears the roof specifically... Recently, however, the rumor went that there's a cure. If you strongly feel an urge to sleep, it is advisable to find a bucket of old... or a pan at least most... the extraction... the Main thing there is that whole... Head to tuck — and sleep itself as God's bosom... Well, laugh, laugh. I see you in a few days, when tired legs start to fall. Wise guy... But you say, what, then, hell, warriors here last time, began to roam in helmets cunning? Well, Yes! Earlier, two years really like, neither hearing nor the spirit, and the last time often! Hat they have a new some guys the body of one was found, told. Mesh inside of such a thin copper wire, attached to the liner. Think about it — what is harness in the hell do she? In General, this "W-W-W" for a reason, I'm telling you. Of anomalies to choose there is nothing special — not the same grounds, on other sites and obezopasit and pieces fatter still there... I think that the approaches they outline. The bridgehead is prepared. To the Sarcophagus to get want, mark my words. Soon, so will giganet — anyone will not find it. Mark my word... Importantly, we're out of here at that time to be...</text>
</string>
<string id="isg_history_3">
 <text>Yes, so I then right up to the edge of the Pripyat reached. Well, I decided first to look around. Found and point a bit higher there was a large boiler with the pipe. Well, he went... kind of neat, you look like Chiki-peaks all — the dust lies, no tracks... got into the furnace and spread: there's the inside of the pipe the steps were. Normal climb, even the soot already and not dirty — petrified. Carefully pop out... Beautiful! Half of the city in your hand! Pulled out the binoculars and look around... (small pause) Well, then... Gathered already, then sliding down, and then the idea slips under the nose, and not looking! Are bent a little over the edge, looking to one side, then to another... wow! That is horrible! In the courtyard of the dwarf loose! Most importantly, I'm down for almost climbed! And that is fine that he does not see me. Only tower I could not carry the can: "Kalash" on the back hanging and the pipe is quite narrow, do not turn. A Makarov, what's under the mouse — shit thing, there is fifty meters, but the difference in height... in short, if you just will not get — but not fall — then just kerdyk. Sitting here thinking. Well, look at the same time, what he's doing. And he does something strange. First, so cheerfully, with a twinkle, rummaging in a pile of trash — only the pieces right and left scattered. And then suddenly as they were, and froze. Like listened. Well, there's quite the mess started. The garbage in that pile itself began to move. The dwarf quickly jumped away, was a column that way, his head in his hands made, hands somehow cleverly twisted and it ka-AK will fly! From all sides!.. Pieces of iron, bricks, roofing material, branches... so His head was covered. Well, I guess everything. Kick the kitten, more will not piss... No way! Two seconds stuff this lay, and then just ka-AK will scatter in all directions! There cutting pipes were, so they live in a concrete fence povtykat. Karl stood still about half a minute, pokumekali himself for something, and then turned around and in the building was drowned. I have a second spirit translated. "Well — I think — enough is enough, it's time to get out of here". And then suddenly the smoke was drawn. And then bake was. Yes, you go to the stump! A fire someone lit from below! After a minute, to breathe there is nothing. Somehow raked to the edge of the pipe, there site no, sit, swung his legs... Just the smoke still eye eats, the air is not enough... in short, we need to go urgently! Thank God I cord always forty feet dragged in case of fire... exactly what a fireman... well, I folded it in half — it is not very thick was — at the very least the pipe is fixed, the neckerchief ripped in half, Bespalko wound on top, and climbed, all the gods prayed... In my head one thought: please don't break! No insurance, nothing, cord the palm of your hand hurts... and, of course, the law of meanness about five meters to the ground it was not enough. Whitefish had. What to do? Oh, and I roared! Lucky, at least not break anything... But stripped and pulled the right foot — be healthy! Then I thought that all ligaments torn. And then pulled out so that the gold medal in the women probably would have won...</text>
</string>
<string id="isg_history_4">
 <text>And then I couldn't believe my eyes. Here, it would seem that there are pretty girls, Yes? But this was... she was... Perfection. Yes. Here. Perfection. Such was the feeling that the world around her in black and white and blurry, it is one only in color and sharpness. As she moved! I also have never seen before. I got a lump in my throat rose. Well she gave up that knowledge! She's here in the Area. Well, Yes, in the Zone. By evening it was... the bus station there are nine separate. First, something in the window on the first floor flashed. I "Kalash" quickly released the safety, and then look — out of the house out... my eyes wanted to wipe — you never know what to expect? And it is suitable. And I'm standing like a fool, staring... machine, however, kept at the ready — a habit already... Then she saw me... Smiled... said Hello... And I listen and do not hear, all staring at her. She's in blue overalls were bright... but not balconista, and almost slinky... her Figure is something fantastic! Only then it dawned on me that I don't really listen to what she says standing and smiling from ear to ear... It turns out, the study group was. Asked if I have the opportunity to help her. Her! Yes, I would in an anomaly for her climbed!.. Said she deals with these, as they are... endemic to the Area. Well plants, which will only then meet. Said he escaped from the guards, because with them no leeway there, and alone came here. I do not know. I believe. Agreed to help — to bring her something. Two days later came as agreed. Five times almost covered, until collected. Go, and in the head one thought: now I will look again! And nothing. I even the house, where it met the saw. So... But for what it was! She just lit up from the inside...</text>
</string>
<string id="isg_history_5">
 <text>So what am I to say something like. When the "debt" that illusa took, well I was near them! Yes, I accidentally generally in those parts turned out to be! My cars have "Fields"at my right front flew: the bolts on the bump cut. For parts complete zero. I pomateritsya, then give, I think, to the plant going, pick the right. Well, there is a kilometer to go, here and there — half an hour! Yes, and I've been there before... Then suddenly I see — "debt"! And not just patrol, but half a Grand! Well, I think, a pancake-compote!.. As they were in the bushes and fell. "If you have noticed and cover start — I think — and then I fucked up". Lay, in short, in the hole, and try not to breathe. And then the shooting! To bursts such shmalyaet, I once heard... when I First base took the old people, remember? In General, lying, listening in both ears... It has Bach, and then also how to kill!.. After five minutes stop, and to me it seems no one goes. Well, I plucked up the nerve, stood up and sensitive in binoculars look. And these are quickly pulled out of the shop... are wrinkled, their blind man's buff for a bunch of drag and illysa on the tarp... lumps alone from illusa left... Atenolol in the Panini. Then I hear the engines roared, and the sound is gone. I have waited for — like one. I inside. Well, it is clear that after the "Debt," fuck what you find! But it would be interesting! Et, I can tell you, it was something! The wall they are almost completely podravje. Beams lying across the floor, a piece of the roof collapsed. Sleeves knee-length natural the shooting range. Blood, lumps some... Useful, however, found nothing — so, two horn full, the machine rolled, I-beam pressed down, not out... About the bolts I, of course, forgot to think... Back to the car, thought for five minutes, removed the bolt from the other wheels... and drove slowly... And leave me there early for half an hour... Hmm...</text>
 </string>
 <string id="history_1">
<text>have you heard about the Explorer? The first of the stalkers. The first in the Area to walk began, and still alive. They say will hold in any point. Another thing is that to find it problematic – do not putting up... and spend far not everyone agrees. The whole lot seems to takes a lot, but if he found it and fixed it, be sure you train it will take place. That's who would grind. He probably saw what was on the radar...</text>
</string>
<string id="history_2">
 <text> you Know, what do you say? In this part, the sleeping Area is almost impossible... Me I am lucky, I can not sleep... and the people of those nightmares happen, that happen, and do not Wake up in the morning... of a broken heart, for example... Who the horses are driven, and who tears the roof specifically... Recently, however, the rumor went that there's a cure. If you strongly feel an urge to sleep, it is advisable to find a bucket of old... or a pan at least most... the extraction... the Main thing there is that whole... Head to tuck – and sleep itself as God's bosom... Well, laugh, laugh. I look at you in a couple of days, when tired legs start to fall. Clever... But do tell me, what, then, hell, warriors here last time, began to roam in helmets cunning? Well, Yes! Earlier, two years really like, neither hearing nor the spirit, and the last time often! Hat they have a new some guys the body of one was found, told. Mesh inside of such a thin copper wire, attached to the liner. Think about it – what is harness in the hell do she? In General, this "W-W-W" for a reason, I'm telling you. Of anomalies to choose there is nothing special – not the same grounds, on other sites and obezopasit and pieces fatter still there... I think that the approaches they outline. The bridgehead is prepared. To the Sarcophagus to get want, mark my words. Soon, so will giganet – anyone will not find it. Mark my words... the Main thing is, you far from here to be...</text>
</string>
<string id="history_3">
 <text> So... I remember someone yesterday about something ask, and I forgot... And I remembered. There is, therefore, curious why the Zone just our eggheads Potter, and the aliens do not show themselves, although there is material on Nobel prize thousand three... Then answer the points. First, why should by here to climb when you can our grant to give, but with such conditions that he is you all I need he bring on a silver platter? But if, secondly, they actually were here, and in large quantities. This is the last two years zabugorny in the Area are afraid to go... happened to them, one major bummer. Now only buy materials Yes information. Pay is good, so a lot of individuals to work for them, and marauders, too... didn't hear about this story? Well, give! The whole Area was buzzing, and you like fell from the sky. In General, the drop was big. Some scholars thirty with half the world... all the luminaries, of course, here and there...Preparing seriously: the money charged is at least one eating place, equipment mountain. Took a platoon of military experts to protect, three of our conductors, shielded armored personnel carriers boarded and sailed away. What... went Back a week later... twelve men on the dead man in the trash armored personnel carriers. The thorn came from the Rotten forest, and there waited... looters... Yes... These do not care where people came out... Put almost everyone. The perimeter only three escaped – two of ours and one egghead. People from the powerful impressions the attic went... Well, him quickly by the collar and treat. He is now the owner says about the Area. Our-nothing else – the experience helped. Although... too, probably, differently moved: one went to the radar and disappeared, and the second on the mainland have moved. Well, the rest of the Area was taken. About the Town-thirty-two heard? That's where they were. At first everything seems quiet it was... well,... They were removed was measured, samples collected, the anomaly devices poked... And then they started insanity. Mass. People slowly began roof to go. I our – the one on the left rest – Who told... throat started own nails to tear, who his head on the wall was broken, and who is just a gun in my mouth, and... And then there's the beasts flooded. Who in themselves were barricaded in the house. Introduced, right? Outside the night and all of the surrounding creature, and people inside the coils fall one after the other. In short, in the morning those who still think I could somehow escaped. Ago drove straight, without a road; even a couple of anomalies hooked... got to Rotten wood... And of those who remained there, no one was ever found. Guys only say that in places dramatically increased controllers. Yes... That's since in Town-thirty-two no fuss, and a foreigner in a Zone and nothing will tempt...</text>
</string>
<string id="history_4">
 <text>show-off to beat and loot to be - are two big differences... Che thought there was money given? Shit! For one's just ugly any gobble or Stalker will fill... Think it is necessary. It is necessary to think, and then even better. The bulls here very long stretches. It is not a channel, without the attic if... well, the thing was. The three of us with a black and Sepoy deceased through the service yard was a road, shorter, cut. Watch the deer some cards. Well, we've snimalis. And he we pass by - not to notice. A little guy, and pulls the bag - bless him. The machine cleverly hangs almost the olives we'll be full. Well, Bruise me - like, let's check mospace, che had it? And I to him: "be Quiet, dumbass! Better watch where he pulls your swag". Che... well, Then the deer fell somewhere - we don't even understand. Well, wait. He twenty minutes later, got out. While standing-has dusted himself down to his Flail back quietly approached and politique of the tapestry was torn down. They began with a black body gut: armor it was cool, and Lopatnic should be cast... I moved my boys I always give, I share. Here, as harenet!.. In short, the patient was not simple: it th-tricky twists that pulled if it is armor someone will shoot. I got out of there quick - only a few people right now on the shot and the explosion will come... Came through a month. From the free end with a Bruise and deer - though the bone. All the zeros. In short, I figured where he dived into the ruins, and he climbed back... Well, passed three rooms - beggar! Look here, in the corner a bunch of beds piled. Why the fuck are there so many chairs? In short, undertook to dig. Raked. Look - my mother was a woman, Luke. Raise, then, cover the candle with a flashlight. Parasite! I was in heaven!.. Well, there was che is my business... Soon left. And the ears would put up - would a dead man was or still barefoot running, cormorants... as some of...</text>
</string>
<string id="history_5">
 <text>In General, that's what my friend told me. Picked it up, in short, in the middle of the night the brass - type ran to the lab, the shipment came. He's sleepy, not cut: what cargo? They told him: you th, alcohol breech drunk? Dead fresh on the table, dinner is served! In short, he comes, and to the table. And there IS... It is, of course, blind man's buff from the Area in his lifetime has seen: and you, torn, and fried-boiled, and mutants caught more than a dozen, and then type in the stomach, the dinner began to walk. In short, at first sight two minutes a man, only the head on the normal guys are like: healthy pumpkin bumpy. Well, the body is a concentration camp fucking skin and bones. But he is then dismantled, and in the beginning, says, look, what a mess: all the wrong way round, stained orange-red stuff - the blood type... These Honduras ammunition have not regretted. Up-OLG... the search for anomalous objects, damn... damn search!.. This, he says, was a cross between a colander and torn warmers... and they obviously do it in their govnodav you had a good time; not an object, a pancake, and a piece of meat in black rags. In short, it is the rest of the night and half the morning humpback. Of course, it turns out, it's the same thing local for the illusionist to know: black cloth, seeing the stalkers, the head meter in girth... Cool what's his face who saw, thought is a type of the benevolent. Not a person he naturally is, only very small: migalki not open and the nose as a pin, although the mouth - big, direct cant at the gate. Go, see, and his head on his chest hangs - there is no strength to hold... mospak... And think about what these creatures eat for lunch. The fungi! Mushrooms! In short, all seen in the Area full of mushrooms, so the "old" swear that these creatures from the juice press. Foodies, damn... And you know what in his bag on the side stashed it? Well? Yes, where are you! In short, the brains had dried. Do you know whose? Audit!..</text>
</string>
<string id="history_6">
 <text>Climb, so in that hangar. Around the dusty, web - all under the roof; the detectors are complete crap, saying that is not something that anyone around but us is not present in nature. Went position on the perimeter to take: Sanya ahead, we cover... And then BZDYN! Hefty beams are of iron, rusty from the ceiling, so one breaks down - and down! How Sasha dodged, he does not know, and this crap is stuck right exactly where he stood. Well, it is, fell and rolled, got up on his feet at all, and so lying Wai da shmalyat! The rest are too scared, stupid, and myself went to sit down in white light. Then Sasha started yelling something about a creature in the corner. I see no critters can't see... well, come on, not surgery, but a specific kind of a mess, bordelero... we Went to these ruins to walk; I went about five minutes, cautiously, so that under these beams no longer come to be. And brad, well, complete nonsense: that one, another something will come they come in parajka you planning on slitting in an empty space. And two had no luck at all: one was on a level floor, and suddenly in the pit fell, the second broken door across the back pulled. Well, then we all wound up - clear well because that creature kind of fun! Turned the psi-protection, to all corners on the gas grenade - well, waiting for who will appear, and the fingers on the descent. Waiting, waiting... And the creature, as it turned out, flying was something... Until we're all together playing the fool, she quietly sat near the ceiling and having a good time, bitch... only Reached us late, and even then almost accidentally. This snake was shattered a couple of beams - pakrashi and came directly at us and welled up, four guys in the cake... Here we got! How Sasha heard the alarm upstairs, on automatic and fired a burst - the most useful fucking reflex! Well here and squeal! We also, clearly, have jumped, given all trunks... Thing stuff top with such cries, that the ears laid. Well, here we soul took: who's butt beat, who is just legs walking, Sanya, so he took a knife to her painful guts to dump... the Commander, of course, all with difficulty, but was pottasium, but it would do this bastard spoons from the floor had to scrape...</text>
</string>
<string id="history_7">
 <text>my partner for this Institute were interested. Painfully, the place is deserted. No animals around, no mutants. But who would go there go, or scared outta my mind, from coils moved down back, or do they no longer seen. Have decided to slowly explore. Left in the morning, and as we got to the place, already beginning to dawn. Left the car in raspotocje, went to the forest to the edge. There stopped, the partner remained downstairs, and I climbed a tree with telescope - look what is happening in the area. See corps, and not quite so abandoned, glass the whole almost all the courtyards in the grass a little, not like in other places - on the belt... it was obvious that I live here, but the utter silence and no movement. Then suddenly just hit the right turn - someone from the machine gun beat short. I optics there. See, on the roof of one of the buildings a strange man like a rat harried rushing and shooting indiscriminately in all directions. One look and I can't understand: he's the only one there was. And here... began... I saw it at a glance. The gun from his hand itself... flew Like wings from the glands grew!.. The man opened his mouth, apparently, yelled something, took out a knife and put it in front of him. And then the lad. - you look, and before him by itself hangs another. So in the air the thorn to him and hanging up, and not holding it no one. What happened next is not to tell the night... five Minutes that guy cut. So little by little, bitches, their mother's leg - there is a cut, then a shot... Poor guy soon covered in blood was... Then, as he was already in his legs began to totter, his knife knocked out; then the guy lifts him into the air as wrap a couple of times... I never saw natural, like a piece of spit... I'm three seconds became wet... and Then... No, everything will not... In General, as I took a breath, about five minutes groping sight in the area. My hands were shaking, optics wet with sweat became... Well, at least one thing! And in the normal range and infrakrasnoi - no-th-th. As I got off, the mate looked at me, and ask want. And when he returned to base, I to brow drinking, do not dry... Then, moved a bit, pumped our - maybe someone about what you heard? Only the people with me began to look askance - hour, not moved? So here goes...</text>
</string>
<string id="history_8">
 <text> Arrived to us here spaz... one Scratch, so skins for five minutes to rest, and he on the fifth point - and relaxes. And how to go - so he's the last ass on earth tears. Well duraclass... behind, and there he overseer for brains DAC! and.... Who is the beginner in this business, remember. The rustle of the breeze there or what is suspicious... even though the rabbit will run... but the bunnies here - God forbid... in short, every second you have to be. To stores and grenades at hand and the machine on the continuous. If I saw that drop immediately polozka; if the bushes something-too loopy, and then ask. Here the course of the young fighter is this: do not outfits hung, and guts will eat, not have time to fart! Yes, about supervisors. Let's say you had shot at rustle and fall immediately, at the same moment! Though on his back, even as. The controller touches, if he sees you, he needs to focus. While sunbathing in the shade, look in both ears - whether rustling, whether what rubbish to you. You can quietly shop Peredelkino, and a grenade is also useful to prepare... if all quiet, count to three and... And knocked! Knocked the hell out! Well, sucked? Oh salazhata... Yourself every second take care of - the only way to survive here and you can...</text>
</string>
<string id="history_9">
 <text> Yes, so I then right up to the edge of the Pripyat reached. Well, I decided first to look around. Found and point a bit higher there was a large boiler with the pipe. Well, he went... kind of neat, you look like Chiki-peaks all - the dust lies, no tracks... got into the furnace and spread: there's the inside of the pipe the steps were. Normal climb, even the soot already and not dirty - petrified. Carefully pop out... Beautiful! Half of the city in your hand! Pulled out the binoculars and look around... (small pause) Well, then... Gathered already, then sliding down, and then the idea slips under the nose, and not looking! Are bent a little over the edge, looking to one side, then to another... wow! That is horrible! In the courtyard of the dwarf loose! Most importantly, I'm down for almost climbed! And that is fine that he does not see me. Only tower I could not carry the can: "Kalash" on the back hanging and the pipe is quite narrow, do not turn. A Makarov, what's under the mouse - shit thing, there is fifty meters, but the difference in height... in short, if you just will not get - but not fall - then just kerdyk. Sitting here thinking. Well, look at the same time, what he's doing. And he does something strange. First, so cheerfully, with a twinkle, rummaging in a pile of trash - only the pieces right and left scattered. And then suddenly as they were, and froze. Like listened. Well, there's quite the mess started. The garbage in that pile itself began to move. The dwarf quickly jumped away, was a column that way, his head in his hands made, hands somehow cleverly twisted and it ka-AK will fly! From all sides!.. Pieces of iron, bricks, roofing material, branches... so His head was covered. Well, I guess everything. Kick the kitten, more will not piss... No way! Two seconds stuff this lay, and then just ka-AK will scatter in all directions! There cutting pipes were, so they live in a concrete fence povtykat. Karlan stood still about half a minute, pokumekali himself for something, and then turned around and in the building was drowned. I have a second spirit translated. "Well - I think - enough is enough, it's time to get out of here". And then suddenly the smoke was drawn. And then bake was. Yes, you go to the stump! A fire someone lit from below! After a minute, to breathe there is nothing. Somehow raked to the edge of the pipe, there site no, sit, swung his legs... Just the smoke still eye eats, the air is not enough... in short, we need to go urgently! Thank God I cord always forty feet dragged in case of fire... exactly what a fireman... well, I folded it in half - it is not very thick was - at the very least the pipe is fixed, the neckerchief ripped in half, Bespalko wound on top, and climbed, all the gods prayed... In my head one thought: please don't break! No insurance, nothing, cord the palm of your hand hurts... and, of course, the law of meanness about five meters to the ground it was not enough. Whitefish had. What to do? Oh, and I roared! Lucky, at least not break anything... But stripped and pulled the right foot - be healthy! Then I thought that all ligaments torn. And then pulled out so that the gold medal in the women probably would have won...</text>
</string>
<string id="history_10">
 <text> And then I couldn't believe my eyes. Here, it would seem that there are pretty girls, Yes? But this was... she was... Perfection. Yes. Here. Perfection. Such was the feeling that the world around her in black and white and blurry, it is one only in color and sharpness. As she moved! I also have never seen before. I got a lump in my throat rose. Well she gave up that knowledge! She's here in the Area. Well, Yes, in the Zone. By evening it was... the bus station there are nine separate. First, something in the window on the first floor flashed. I "Kalash" quickly released the safety, and then look - out of the house out... my eyes wanted to wipe - you never know what to expect? And it is suitable. And I'm standing like a fool, staring... machine, however, kept at the ready - a habit already... Then she saw me... Smiled... said Hello... And I listen and do not hear, all staring at her. She's in blue overalls were bright... but not balconista, and almost slinky... her Figure is something fantastic! Only then it dawned on me that I don't really listen to what she says standing and smiling from ear to ear... It turns out, the study group was. Asked if I have the opportunity to help her. Her! Yes, I would in an anomaly for her climbed!.. Said she deals with these, as they are... endemic to the Area. Well plants, which will only then meet. Said he escaped from the guards, because with them no leeway there, and alone came here. I do not know. I believe. Agreed to help - to bring her something. Two days later came as agreed. Five times almost covered, until collected. Go, and in the head one thought: now I will look again! And nothing. I even the house, where it met the saw. So... But for what it was! She just lit up from the inside...</text>
</string>
<string id="history_11">
<text>Brothers, the Monolith called me last night. I talked to him. He was beautiful in his greatness. I almost went blind, but his light filled me with great force! I know, I feel that his power is with us! He told me that to defeat the evil needs strong faith. He said that his power will fill only correct. He also let me know that our victory is near!</text>
</string>
<string id="history_12">
 <text>Brothers, you have heard that recently some bad crept to the antennas? The monolith has sent us brothers and in time they noticed. One got killed right away. The other two fled. Briefs. They are all cowards. Only true faith leaves no room for fear! Two managed to escape, but the Monolith is wise and omniscient. So they need him alive.</text>
</string>
<string id="history_13">
<text>Brothers, we patrolled the outskirts of the Black Forest, and encountered a wrong-alone. He started to turn, so we didn't kill him, but he was still half in his animal state... I know a wise a Monolith made it for all of us: he again showed us the true face of their enemies. Now our faith was strengthened! Is coming, brothers!.. Nearing victory over the infidels, and then the Monolith will fulfill our deepest desire! True devotees, he will bring him near to himself, to his glory, his greatness! We always arrive in the radiance of him. </text>
</string>
 <string id="history_14">
 <text>Brothers, recently, Monolith has been tested my faith and I almost went astray. But I survived! Praise The Monolith! Testing makes us strong! We were coming back from Dark Valley and I'm a little behind the brethren. The evil took advantage of this and suddenly began to play with me. And... I doubted. The true image is distorted: the enemy whispered to me that the Monolith uses us as slaves. But then I realized: this is a test. I remembered the power and the radiance of the Monolith and then my will and confidence back. Since then, I am not afraid of any test and do not know doubt. Praise The Monolith!</text>
</string>
 <string id="history_15">
 <text>I was in the Dark Valley. There's a lot of infidels, that the power of the Monolith has not reached these places. We guarded. The night we were attacked. We fought fiercely with these animals. Merit brothers were great: coming soon Monolith called them to himself. For me he prepared another test. My gun did not shoot. But the Monolith said to me: "You are with me, and my strength is with you. If you're firm in your faith, you will crush my enemies and get close to me!". Then I became a shadow. I crouched and walked them right. Stupid spies did not notice anything. They thought through with us and laughed at the empty bodies of our brothers. But I've seen them from the back. And then out of my hands hit the power of the Monolith. So he killed them all. I am happy to serve you, Perfect!</text>
</string>
</string_table>