<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_1_name">
		<text>Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_1_desc">
		<text>Important documents. Return them for your reward.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_2_name">
		<text>Locked Case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_2_desc">
		<text>A locked case. Not sure what's inside but it's heavy. Better be worth it lugging this thing around.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_3_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_3_desc">
		<text>An encrypted PDA. You have been promised a reward for its return.</text>
	</string>



<string id="bad_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>Prototype developed by scientists to protect people from psi-emissions. Needs adjusting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bad_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Uncalibrated psi-helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="good_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>Prototype developed by scientists to protect people from psi-emissions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="good_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Psi-helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_short_desc">
		<text>Doctor's key to a secret stash in Pripyat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_name">
		<text>Doctor's key</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_desc">
		<text>A key with 'Hotel Polissya – Room 26' engraved on side.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_desc">
		<text>Worn manuscript in leather binding. Written by Strelok himself.\nJudging by the headings alone, it might explain some of the Zone's secrets.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_pda_name">
		<text>Doctor's notes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_pda_desc">
		<text>'Just some notes about old men's conspiracy theories'.\n\nThere are rumours that the Agroprom Institute was used as a front for an unofficial lab in the years preceding the 2006 year accident. This lab hosted a number of very unusual experiments. The traders have dug up a lot of information about these laboratories. I met with the Barkeep, he says he sent Duty scouts to get into the underground vaults of the Dark Valley, called X18, but they disappeared. There are another rumours regarding a 'psi-brain' mechanism. The whole neighbourhood in Yantar is under the influence of that piece of trash: it zombified everyone who came within range. There is another mechanism in the Red Forest radar underground, called lab X19, and that is what is likely to be the Brain Scorcher. There is evidence to suggest that the presence of the Brain Scorcher intentionally blocks the road to the North, but no one knows exactly what it is. The Barkeep believes that the Brain Scorcher is man-made, and these mechanisms are not always operating at full strength. He thinks there are periods when their power is lowered to cool down the apparatus. It's time to visit all the underground laboratories in the Zone and find out what kind of secrets they are hiding. Too bad, that I'm too old for this shit. I wish Strelok would be still around, but damn, he disappeared years ago.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_name">
		<text>Strelok's manuscript</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_decoder_desc">
		<text>A powerful electronic lock-pick. Strangely enough, it does not seem to be an all-purpose thieves' instrument. Rather, it seems to have been created with a specific electronic lock in mind and can't be used to override anything else.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_decoder_name">
		<text>Decoder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pri_decoder_docs_conclusion_txt">
		<text>The manuscript contains a short report on how Fang and Strelok infiltrated a hidden laboratory and their journey there. It makes mention of large Monolith presence in and around the Chernobyl NPP. More specifically under the concrete sarcophagus, also suggesting it may be their base of operations but with the intent to hide something. Reading further it states that they discovered laboratory hidden further in the north under the generators, however they were unable to gain access at the time of writing as they required the use of a decoder.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_quest_case_02_desc">
		<text>A fireproof briefcase containing military documents and reports on investigations performed near Agroprom. The reports talk in detail about how machinery and equipment has gone missing from the institute, and how the results of the investigations on their whereabouts were apparently falsified.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_quest_case_02_name">
		<text>Military documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x18_name">
		<text>Biology research report</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x18_desc">
		<text>The report details the study of biological samples sent from Lab X-18. The samples were subjected to informational field effects of varying intensities. The report meticulously describes the mutation of living beings following exposure to emissions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x16_desc">
		<text>The documents refer to one of the side discoveries of bio-research, specifically the discovery that living creatures are able to generate directed psi-emissions. A biological field emitter, essentially a giant brain, was grown as part of the research conducted in Lab X-16.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x16_name">
		<text>Psi research documents</text>
	</string>
		<string id="item_doc_x10_desc">
		<text>The documents describe the technical characteristics of an antenna and how they deviate from their planned designs. There is a note on the reverse side which indicates that these documents were prepared in Lab X-19.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x10_name">
		<text>Rainbow emitter documents</text>
	</string>
		<string id="item_doc_x8_desc">
		<text>The document refers to the transfer of the research team and all materials to another laboratory far in the north, which will be used to research matters relating to the influence of the noosphere. To enter the lab, use the date of the accident as the code (ddmmyyyy).\n\nThe research team comprised: N.A. Lebedev, E.F. Kalancha and V.I. Suslov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x8_name">
		<text>Order of Transfer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_jup_ug_desc">
		<text>The notebook contains a detailed description of an experiment assessing a psi-field's effect on an object in another hemisphere. A group of scientists in the Caribbean received the signal, but it was distorted. The signal was altered in a strange way, as though corrected by someone. A possible explanation is that the noosphere theory is correct and the changes were made by the noosphere.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_jup_ug_name">
		<text>Experiment notebook</text>
	</string>
		<string id="item_doc_mon_con_name">
		<text>Prototype weapon report</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_mon_con_name_desc">
		<text>Documents which describe the operating mechanism and main technical characteristics of a more advanced electromagnetic device.\nThere is a note inside the documents which reads: 'Documents must be returned to X8, the central laboratory. I will be busy, so deliver them yourself. — N. Lebedev'</text>
	</string>

<string id="jup_b47_merc_pda">
	<text>PDA Digger</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_b47_merc_pda_desc">
	<text>Band its settled in the cemetery of technology. Recently, some Sultan came, looked at the preparation of the brothers and the strengthening of the point. They said something about Valerian and Zvezdochet, I was far away, did not quite hear. How to get my affairs to the Landfill-I'll go along with Gray's group to the Barman. He surely will clarify the situation.\n Wild Ex.</text>
	</string>
<string id="st_device_flash_snag">
	<text>PDA Valeriana</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_flash_snag_descr">
	<text>Among all idiotic garbage, there is information about a man named Sakharov, allegedly he is making a psi helmet for passage through zones of increased radiation. I'll have to visit him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_pda_port_bandit_leader">
	<text>KPK Voronin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_pda_port_bandit_leader_descr">
	<text>I order you to block all the ex its from the dungeon, so that no creature from there crawls out! To send a detachment of professional fighters to the burrow to deter evil spirits, the next day will come a replacement group.\n General Voronin.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_pda_zat_b5_dealer_desc">
	<text>A stalker came to us, called Fang. In appearance, like, a mercenary, but stripe wore stalker. He asked Novikov to give him a pair of capacitors and textolite plates. I do not know why the hell they are to him, but he paid well. I'll send a scout for him, let him trace it to the border of the Swamp.\n Cold.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_pda_zat_b5_dealer_name">
	<text>PDA Coldness</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b10_notes_01_desc">
	<text>Ghost, I'm taking my stuff. Special thanks for the machine-I without it as without hands. In return I leave the kit of medicines from the Doctor. Now I'm going to a meeting with Zvezdochet: he managed to assemble the decoder. If you manage, we'll meet in our safe house.\n Arrows.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b10_notes_01_name">
	<text>Note to the Ghost</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b10_notes_02_desc">
	<text>Fang, the second decoder crashed when I fell into the hole at the exit of X-16. If there were not one stalker, I would have died. While I'm sitting at Sakharov's place, I'll patch up my wounds. Before going to the Laboratory, I spoke with the Guide, he said that he would stay with the Steller for a while with Zvezdochet. I hope, you will have time to catch him there.\n Ghost.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b10_notes_02_name">
	<text>Note to Fang</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b10_notes_03_desc">
	<text>Shooter, I cannot wait for you anymore-I have a whole pack on my tail. I'm on my way to Pripyat. If I do not come back, tap the Ghost and say, let it also stomp on our apartment. Everything, be it!\n Fang.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b10_notes_03_name">
	<text>Arrow note</text>
	</string>
<string id="st_jup_b205_sokolov_note_desc">
	<text>On the notebook sheet in the cage written all sorts of corollas and notes, apparently, these are the caches of Rabinovich with supplies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b205_sokolov_note_name">
	<text>Rabinovich's note</text>
	</string>
<string id="st_jup_b207_merc_pda_with_contract_desc">
	<text>Among the encrypted data there are references to the transition of the Aremayan Warehouses-Radar and back. Also there is a tip for some countryman.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b207_merc_pda_with_contract_name">
	<text>Ghost's Handheld</text>
	</string>
<string id="st_jup_b46_duty_founder_pda_desc">
	<text>the flash-drive has a recent correspondence with Zvezdochet and Rifleman. In one of the dialogues there are transitions to the Red Forest, Limansk, the Hospital and the Overpass. Reverse transitions are also included.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b46_duty_founder_pda_name">
	<text>PDA Fang</text>
	</string>
<string id="st_pri_b306_envoy_pda_desc">
	<text>the last entry on the flash-drive reads: Garin returned not so long ago, he said that he was on the road to Zaton, that he had a cement plant. It will be necessary to collect an expedition group and study the local anomalies there.\n German.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pri_b306_envoy_pda_name">
	<text>Herman's PDA</text>
	</string>
<string id="st_pri_b36_monolith_hiding_place_pda_desc">
	<text>There are a lot of records in the flash-drive that do not have an obvious meaning, but one still attracts attention: Recently, Skadovsk himself came to the Guide himself. He told the group of 'Debtors' and the military transition Pripyat. Reported to this beard, he wants to carry out the operation to clean up, in order to avoid attacks from both sides. Coordinates I'll write down the transition, I'll never forget it.\n Pilot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pri_b36_monolith_hiding_place_pda_name">
	<text>KPK of the Pilot</text>
	</string>
<string id="st_zat_b20_noah_pda_desc">
	<text>Arranged along the perimeter of small groups, for safety. Monoliths every day try to take us by storm, but we still keep the defenses. Sooner or later we will have to go on the offensive, I'm afraid only that losses cannot be avoided.\n Colonel Kowalski.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_b20_noah_pda_name">
	<text>Kovalsky's handheld computer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_b40_notebook_desc">
	<text>the last outgoing message:\n A fanatic attack was committed a few hours ago. We take everything we can, and we go to the Chernobyl nuclear power plant, through the center of Pripyat. Suslov managed to find a short road to the west, we move there. I hope that's enough for us to stop the Arrow.\n D. Lebedev.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_b40_notebook_name">
	<text>Laptop Lebedev</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_b40_pda_1_desc">
	<text>I'm scared. Kowalski does everything necessary for the security of our camp, but the monoliths will not stop! the Shooter came recently, gave us some supplies and left somewhere. We sit here as if on needles, and these staff freaks do not even plan to take us away from here! When it's all over, I'm gone. in civil aviation. I've had enough of this damned Zone!\n Sokolov ON</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_b40_pda_1_name">
	<text>PDA Sokolov</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_b40_pda_2_name">
	<text>KPK Rogovets</text>
	</string>
<string id="st_zat_b40_pda_2_desc">
	<text>Every day I look at the wounded, and every twelve hours new sacrifices come to me. Lord, give me strength not to go insane..\n Lieutenant Rogovets.</text>
	</string>
<string id="zat_b39_joker_pda_description">
	<text>the shooter Capt a lot of information related to the Zone. She certainly will be interested in influential merchants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b39_joker_pda_name">
	<text>PDA Arrow</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b44_barge_pda_desc">
	<text>Half of the case is done, it remains to destroy the fanatics in the north and we can safely return home. I hope I'll bring the guys out of this baked alive and unharmed./N Major 'Quartet' Chetverikov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b44_barge_pda_name">
	<text>flash-drive Quartet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_medic_pda_desc">
	<text>Semetsky Capt a lot of secrets, including the transitions to the Generators and the coordinates of the secret Laboratory.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_medic_pda">
	<text>KPK Semetsky</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b202_bandit_pda">
	<text>PDA Vasil</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b202_bandit_pda_descr">
	<text>Heck! the quartet appointed me as the curator of the Chernobyl clean-up operation, but I'm not ready for such a thing! I spat on everything, I go to the Cordon.\n Brigadier Vasil.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>