<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_1_name">
<text>Box in the basement</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_1_descr">
<text>Threw things in the basement near a door marked "High voltage". Wait no time, and then be sure to take.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_2_name">
<text>in the switchboard Nychka</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_2_descr">
<text>On the second floor of an abandoned factory in the switchboard staged stash. Gather up the swag a little more, then all at once the huckster pen.</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_3_name">
<text>Stash at the dead end of the collector</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_3_descr">
<text>Accidentally wandered into a dead end collector under the base and stashed the stuff some the crossbar pipe.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_4_name">
<text>Stash in the pipe</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_4_descr">
<text>On the ground floor, zabroshennogo factory, near the stairs, made a hiding place in the pipe.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_5_name">
<text>Pipe under the tank</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_5_descr">
<text>On the farm under the tank pruning pipes hidden, like a pack of dogs fell on a tail. The case will be taken.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_6_name">
<text>Stash at the factory</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_6_descr">
<text>Stash of the world in an abandoned factory! Directly in front of the crosspiece with a valve. The main thing - with the other as not to confuse.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_7_name">
<text>Backpack in the cab</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_7_descr">
<text>it would be Necessary for the backpack to its inverted in the cab of the KAMAZ back. Had him there to throw to from his pursuers to leave.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_8_name">
<text>a Cache under the tree</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_8_descr">
<text>do Not forget the tree under which things took off. There are, however, the entrance to the manifold next, but still can be confused.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_9_name">
<text>Backpack on a tree</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_9_descr">
 <text>All of your caches on the ground in the different holes do, but I'm a tree-organized - figure who would think to look there.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_10_name">
<text>the Secret under the roof of</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_10_descr">
<text>For my stash, I am calm: if anyone would think to look for him so high, you will need more beams to it jump, like a squirrel.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_11_name">
<text>Stash in the tower</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_11_descr">
 <text>Backpack decided from his partner to stash the type dropped on the road. This sucker happened. On the barrel of the water tower is my swag, I was waiting for.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_12_name">
<text>Backpack in the Elevator</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_12_descr">
<text>How the entanglement with the shooting, especially the swag to hide was not. Threw the backpack in the "gut" under the boards. The time will come - will come for him.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_13_name">
<text>small box</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_13_descr">
<text>Found a case from-under bench tools, hid his treasures there for a while. Will be the case - will transfer to normal caches.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_14_name">
<text>safe in the factory</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_14_descr">
<text>If someone reads this entry, therefore, kill me. So that's what I say about the stash in the safe: to you, beast, I could not open!</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_15_descr">
 <text>didn't get out if this mess alive, and that put things in a rusty safe in an abandoned farm. Now it's time to pick them up.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_16_name">
<text>tree Stump on the island</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_16_descr">
<text>my Friend carried a bunch of good, when he came to the Moors in the ambush. He died, but I had to tell that part of the swag in a rotten tree stump hid near the antenna. Will have to pick up. </text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_17_name">
<text>Rotten log</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_17_descr">
<text>I do Not believe your partner: it seems to me he Rob me going. I had him the swag to hide. Near the bridge on the island in the log of my stash - I hope he will not find it.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_18_name">
<text>Rotten tree stump</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_18_descr">
<text>In the hollow of a stump near the old farm threw something when boars skedaddle.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_19_name">
<text>tree Stump near the hill</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_19_descr">
<text>At the foot of the hill behind the marsh made a hiding place under an old stump. Again good call, throw off, there is still something.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_20_name">
<text>tree Stump near the jetty</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_20_descr">
<text>I have Seen this is happening to hemp on the island is constantly che runs. Probably nicked all their possessions, Zhlobin. Like something was coming there, even if only a bit more lumped.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_21_name">
<text>the Old "Zaporozhets"</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_21_descr">
<text>These weirdoes are wondering where their welcome of the caches go? That's hilarious! And I have it in the cockpit of the old "Constipation" near the Marshes nikau. Fig there who turn up to search.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_1_name">
<text>Switchboard at the plant</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_1_descr">
<text>Androginnogo PDA rewrote that at the plant in a rickety switchboard he hid the swag, when Methodrule cover was.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_2_name">
 <text>Shield for transformer</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_2_descr">
<text>When was the "hewing" at the factory, threw it quick to the plate on the transformer.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_3_name">
<text>Case at the factory</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_3_descr">
<text>Found in the hangar a box of tools. Something inside rattled, but to disclose did not, thrown there until the next time.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_4_name">
<text>Box truck</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_yantar_treasure_4_descr">
<text>Nice place for a cache. In exactly between the cab and the body. Again - the geeks and the radiation guard.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_5_name">
<text>Stash at the fence</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_5_descr">
<text>Something hid the articulation of the pipes from a construction trailer near the fence.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_6_name">
<text>small Things in the pipe</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_6_descr">
 <text>the Most valuable is carried away, and small things took off in a steel room with a hole in the wall.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_7_name">
<text>Backpack near the entrance</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_7_descr">
<text>Stuffed a backpack full of swag, but at the entrance I had to throw in ruins. Managed there for someone to get or not?</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_8_name">
<text>a Cache in a ventilation shaft</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_8_descr">
 <text>This is Owl. Remember, Toja, coordinates and landmark - backpack inside the ventilation pipe near the broken wall of the compound!</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_9_name">
<text>Backpack under the seat</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_9_descr">
<text>Time to think was not: threw a swag under the seat drove in a rusty UAZ</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_10_name">
<text>Stash at the reducer of crane</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_10_descr">
 <text>I don't know why the hell did this Verhoture stash did. Now can't reach it, damn it.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_11_name">
<text>Cache in the box</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_11_descr">
<text>the best cache in the Zone, my safety Deposit box at the plant.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_12_name">
<text>Hollow log</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_12_descr">
<text>"Barb" hid his stash in an empty log.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_13_name">
 <text>log under the hill</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_13_descr">
<text>Like a zombie from the factory flooded, had to part with the swag and hide in a log at the base of the hill.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_14_name">
<text>tree Stump near the tower</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_14_descr">
<text>In the hollow of a stump on the hill with a high-voltage tower fouled another secret stash. And everyone thinks I'm there to admire the views I get on... assholes.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_17_name">
<text>Trumpet</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_gar_treasure_17_descr">
<text>trumpet in the mountain of radioactive waste have made a hiding place.</text>
</string>
	<string id="st_gar_treasure_18_name">
<text>Pipe at the motor</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_18_descr">
<text>The "dead" motor in the dump pipe with the swag.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_1_name">
<text>the cross</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_1_descr">
<text>Agroprom, Bush, cross. Beneath him in the grave.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_2_name">
<text>electrical panel in the workshop</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_2_descr">
 <text>Dried, bitch, all the loot for himself. Gray-BA-s ' grandfather! A little hiding from him the odds and ends in the plate shop on the second floor.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_3_name">
<text>Tractor</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_4_name">
<text>vehicle</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_4_descr">
<text>In the body of the commander "Bobby" hide your odds and ends. While the machine is broken, I think most people roam.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_5_name">
<text>Case under train car</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_agr_treasure_5_descr">
<text>In the bag for the tools under the car in the Agricultural industry.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_6_name">
<text>a Bus stop</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_6_descr">
<text>Toolbox in the bus at a stop near the base of the neutrals.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_3_descr">
<text>timokha fixed the tractor - drunk night at the skate Zone until the bloodsucker not to run. Skedaddle so that he forgot the box with the swag.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_7_name">
 <text>Pipe in rubble</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_7_descr">
<text>Littered the entrance to the dungeon, pipe bend, caches.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_8_name">
<text>no man's backpack</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_9_name">
<text>Base, the stalkers</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_9_descr">
<text>Backpack threw on the branching of the tree, and then immediately realize that I Vitale moved. You can get pipes with a base of neutrals.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_8_descr">
 <text>Spotted it on the tree at the base of "Debt", but there was no time for him to climb.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_10_name">
<text>the Pipe near the swamps</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_11_name">
<text>Lost backpack</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_11_descr">
<text>Resting after a hike. Among the stones forgot your backpack. Find time - I'll go for it.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_12_name">
<text>Backpack installer</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_12_descr">
 <text>And it was on that fucking tower to climb! Had on the way the backpack in the bushes to lose, while our dogs are not stripped.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_10_descr">
<text>Nychka near the marshes in the pipe - there is a backpack with a swag.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_13_name">
<text>safe in bushes</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_13_descr">
<text>Under the rain dragged across the ravine a safe with belongings there and left, and the legs on the clay went home, as cows.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_14_name">
<text>the Beam in the suburbs</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_15_name">
<text>Easter eggs</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_15_descr">
<text>Anton at Easter are forced in the rain hiding places for the clan to do. One such "Easter egg" I log hang.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_treasure_14_descr">
<text>In this backwater, hardly anyone would think to look in the log cache.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_treasure_1_name">
<text>Pipe in the control room</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_treasure_1_descr">
 <text>Hidden in a tube of extra things when I padapella creatures: without them it was easier to escape.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_treasure_2_name">
<text>backpack in the anomaly</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_treasure_2_descr">
<text>When passed over the bridge, my backpack fell down in your place. Was not able to get it.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_treasure_4_name">
<text>Backpack on the corpse</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_treasure_4_descr">
 <text>Malice small mutants resemble either rats, or any other rodents killed my friend. I myself just did get lucky, next to the staircase was.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_treasure_5_name">
<text>Backpack under stairs</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_treasure_5_descr">
<text>Saw a large black backpack under the stairs in the water, but we were afraid to climb up there and take away: nearby big anomaly.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_1_name">
<text>Under the cross on the hill</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_1_descr">
 <text>I Hid the swag on the hill under the false tomb Stalker.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_2_name">
<text>the Casket over the bridge</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_2_descr">
<text>Where the cross beams bridge farms, there Packed my swag in the chest. And she was swamped, while there climbed! But no one can find.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_3_name">
<text>Pipe under vyvoroten</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_3_descr">
 <text>the Camp stood not far from the village of newcomers, I hid the swag in the pipe under a fallen tree. Take, as the time comes.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_15_name">
<text>Pipe in the tunnel</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_15_descr">
<text>Throw in the anomaly of trash and by mistake threw the pipe, inside of which hid the swag. So they lay there, gathering dust.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_4_name">
<text>Backpack in the chimney</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_4_descr">
 <text>Even when a novice was organized a secret stash in the chimney. Even I do not remember what is in there.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_5_name">
<text>Stash in a tree</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_5_descr">
<text>Watched from the tree for ATP, left at the top of the backpack. On the branch side of a hill to climb easier.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_6_name">
<text>the locomotive</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_6_descr">
 <text>Under the engine, next to the mound, threw his backpack with the good, when the elder ordered quickly for Nikolaev to blow.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_7_name">
<text>Backpack in the bushes</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_7_descr">
<text>Ran into the mob and the night in the shootout quick feet to do had. Backpack tossed between the boulders, behind a Bush.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_8_name">
<text>Backpack under the wood</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_8_descr">
 <text>Laid the firewood stash from the two-storey building opposite the farm.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_16_name">
<text>safe in the tube</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_17_name">
<text>safe in the database</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_seif_03_0000_desc_name">
<text>On the basis of the neutrals on the cordon ZIL keeps his junk in the box.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_16_descr">
<text>At the dump near the Village of Novikov with Nick made the stash in the safe.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_9_name">
<text>Cache log</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_esc_treasure_9_descr">
<text>How dogs attacked, she had no choice: he hid the swag in the blasted tree in the middle of the field and ran toward the camp.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_10_name">
<text>Nychka in log</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_10_descr">
<text>Rewrote the deceased Stalker the coordinates of his stash in the log after the farm.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_11_name">
<text>tree Stump in spruce forest</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_11_descr">
 <text>In old stump, around which the trees are growing, hid Druganov a simple swag.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_12_name">
<text>tree Stump near the village of</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_12_descr">
<text>Stash far do not: close to Village newcomers found a nice stump with a hollow in it and hide their findings.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_13_name">
<text>tree Stump in the forest</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_13_descr">
 <text>Sidorovich was asked to make a cache near a checkpoint in front of a Large earth - for a beginner some. So I hid everything under a stump at the hill.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_14_name">
<text>tree Stump on the Cordon</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_14_descr">
<text>going into a Landfill, put the stump in the forest to the mob has not got.</text>
</string>

<string id="st_gar_treasure_1_name">
<text>electrical panel in the garbage</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_1_descr">
 <text>snuck some for a night, then to sell at a Flea market. Feel in the box of the fuse box near the cab of a fallen crane.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_2_name">
<text>Shield under cover</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_2_descr">
<text>Drive somehow on the black market that the neighborhood under a canopy in the electrical shield is stashed.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_16_name">
<text>electrical panel in the Junkyard</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_16_descr">
<text>Habr sanican the lid of the fuse box in the mountain of garbage</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_gar_treasure_3_name">
<text>Pipe in the dustbin</text>
</string>
	<string id="st_gar_treasure_3_descr">
<text>In a piece of pipe shoved their possessions, that is not selected.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_4_name">
<text>Pipe at the base of the crane</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_4_descr">
<text>pipe at the base of the destroyed crane hid himself small things just in case.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_5_name">
<text>Backpack under the tree</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_19_name">
<text>Backpack in the crane cabin</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_19_descr">
 <text>I Hid the backpack in the cabin, when the crane stood. Now you can not get.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_5_descr">
<text>ummm your backpack with the contents stashed under the tree.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_20_name">
<text>Caches from the enemies</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_20_descr">
<text>To the swag they had no enemies, threw the backpack in a pile of radioactive debris.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_6_name">
<text>Stash at the cemetery equipment</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_6_descr">
 <text>Near the cemetery infected equipment under a concrete slab was thrown up. There is always someone climbs, so we'd better all take.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_7_name">
<text>the Roof of the locomotive</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_7_descr">
<text>On the roof of the locomotive was attached to your backpack. To get from the mound to easily and thus you can not see.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_8_name">
<text>safe in the puddle</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_8_descr">
 <text>So I think, few people will climb in a puddle poking around in the flooded vault. For the first time, a good place to stash it.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_9_name">
<text>safe under the base</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_9_descr">
<text>Near the radiation hazard put in the safe swag. I don't think there is a safecracker-suicide!</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_10_name">
<text>Hollow log</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_10_descr">
<text>Me safe was the hollow of a tree near the camp.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_11_name">
<text>Log behind the oak</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_11_descr">
<text>Kolyan old threw that Kweli swag hides in a log during the dry oak.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_12_name">
<text>a Log in the bushes</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_12_descr">
<text>stashed the stuff in a log in the bushes, to whom the eye is not caught.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_13_name">
<text>the Hiding place of the fugitives</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_13_descr">
 <text>digger one decided swag to carry, but on him fell the Shepherd with their Boyfriends. Dude decided to do, only the stuff not found. And I noticed a stump that swag preteren was.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_14_name">
<text>Stash in the suburbs</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_14_descr">
<text>On the outskirts fouled nest egg in a rotten stump, if I was someone from their consume.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_15_name">
<text>a Cache at the base</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_15_descr">
 <text>Who as, but I'm a swag under the noses of Yoga are hiding near the fence under an old stump.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_hos_treasure_1_name">
<text>the fuse box is in the hospital</text>
</string>
<string id="st_hos_treasure_1_descr">
<text>did reserve for your group in the distribution panel on the first floor of the hospital.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_hos_treasure_2_name">
<text>Backpack under stairs</text>
</string>
<string id="st_hos_treasure_2_descr">
<text>storming second floor had hands from the things of the release.</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_hos_treasure_3_name">
<text>Barricades in the corridor</text>
</string>
<string id="st_hos_treasure_3_descr">
<text>the Shoot had to, so I hid the swag in the old safe. Look in the barricades along the corridor on the second floor of the hospital.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_3_name">
<text>Pipe in the sewers</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_3_descr">
<text>In the sewer found some hiding place. As back, take.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_6_name">
<text>the Bag in an alcove</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_5_name">
 <text>the Valise in the attic</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_5_descr">
<text>Two days from the interview shoot. In the end drove us under the roof, and then just our fit. I there case noticed, but in the confusion I forgot it in the attic.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_6_descr">
<text>was a RAID by th yard, noticed the sakvoyazhika near the fence.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_7_name">
<text>Pipe under the Car</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_8_name">
<text>garage</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_8_descr">
 <text>Saw someone hiding behind the garages, only to look did not. To watch in a big pipe behind the tree.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_1_name">
<text>Pipe in the container</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_1_descr">
<text>we Squeezed in some yard-it in the pipe where the dumpster like it was something. How things come to look.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_7_descr">
<text>pipe under the Car sticking out of some sack of shit. No time to check it. Alive I will investigate.</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_lim_treasure_9_name">
<text>Backpack under the glove compartment</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_9_descr">
<text>In the old "the Muscovite" under the dashboard threw the backpack the guy Jug.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_2_name">
<text>Backpack under the fence</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_14_name">
<text>Things wounded</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_14_descr">
<text>break out Sanka, when climbed over the wall. Had his backpack to throw in order to save itself.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_2_descr">
 <text>getting away, threw the backpack under the fence here.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_10_name">
<text>Backpack killed</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_10_descr">
<text>the New guy next to me with a grenade covered, dude has had it. And backpack it to Dan under the bridge threw. He's already dead to the bulb, and then we might suffice.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_11_name">
<text>safe in garage</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_11_descr">
 <text>Searched for the fugitive in the garage, I came across one at the safe. It will be necessary later to open it.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_12_name">
<text>Prikopat log</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_12_descr">
<text>Before he stopped this monster, I noticed that it is something outside of the log gazebo was busy.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_13_name">
<text>the Bundle in a tree stump</text>
</string>
<string id="st_lim_treasure_13_descr">
<text>In the hollow of the stump like a bundle of some kind flashed, when we went on the attack.</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_mar_treasure_1_name">
<text>Nychka near the bunker</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_1_descr">
<text>As a gang Oblique on the trail thought I hatch from a bunker under the swamp two steps from the abandoned ATP imbedded a stash of swag.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_2_name">
<text>a Box under the tower</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_2_descr">
<text>Demolished until all the swag in the cache under one of the HV towers.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_3_name">
<text>Box in the cab of the ZIL</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_mar_treasure_3_descr">
<text>Sanya Lame from the bench brought, we put something valuable and threw it in the rusty cab of the ZIL.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_4_name">
<text>Tube station</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_4_descr">
<text>In the old pumping station in the middle of the moor had hid in the bell near the valve.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_6_name">
<text>Pipe in swamp</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_6_descr">
 <text>I'm Sick of these swamps on himself to carry the swag, so I threw on one island in a submerged pipe with a valve. In the reeds still figure who is without the exact coordinates you will find.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_5_name">
<text>Backpack in the swamps</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_5_descr">
<text>Hardly of swamp thing came off, but the backpack is dropped. Reluctance to go there again, but maybe push.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_8_name">
<text>Submerged safe</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_8_descr">
 <text>Near the destroyed bridge pritupleny the safe is. Ventured back all their odds and ends to throw.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_7_name">
<text>Backpack in reeds</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_7_descr">
<text>In the reeds dropped the backpack when he fought off wild boars. No guidelines, well at least the coordinates of the place immediately hammered.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_10_name">
<text>Left swag</text>
</string>
	<string id="st_mar_treasure_10_descr">
<text>From under the nose of one sucker backpack with swag stolen. Very far away: not to burn, had to throw in near the reeds.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_9_name">
<text>tree Stump</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_9_descr">
<text>Decided that the swag will be put in at the dry stump of a tree. How will shedding with Wetlands, will be taken.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_12_name">
<text>the Beam from the tower</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_12_descr">
 <text>Split a tree near high-voltage towers.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_11_name">
<text>death mask</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_11_descr">
<text>the Dead people are more reliable than alive. My caches in the cemetery on the far left grave, mask noted.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_14_name">
<text>Wooden cross</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_14_descr">
<text>In the grave with only a wooden cross in a row in the churchyard was set aside for a rainy day a small stash.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_13_name">
<text>Church wood</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_13_descr">
<text>Under God's supervision hid my stuff in a cracked beam.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_16_name">
<text>Cache in reeds</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_16_descr">
<text>Left the backpack near the Church in the reeds, but now even the coordinates can not be found.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_15_name">
<text>safe in the mud</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_15_descr">
 <text>On the banks of the swamp near the Church put it in a safe all their findings to the robbers did not get.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_18_name">
<text>the Bag under the stove</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_18_descr">
<text>Stirlitz stoked the stove is the third day. On the fourth she drowned. In it I hid your sakvoyazhika.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_17_name">
<text>the Junk in the ZAZ</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_17_descr">
 <text>Midnight sat on the roof, "Cossacks" until our not come. I didn't know who until we first get because thrown somewhere near your stuff. In daylight it will be necessary to find.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_20_name">
<text>Stump "glands"</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_20_descr">
<text>took Place at the "glands" when the firing was heard. I my things quickly in the stump behind the boulders and hid.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_19_name">
<text>Pipe from the tank</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_19_descr">
 <text>Collected all the boys in the sleeve pipe (with a valve) from the tank to the Swamps goes.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_22_name">
<text>backpack on the mattress</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_22_descr">
<text>Lech, stupid stupid, I forgot your backpack where sleep - sunken boat next to the mattress.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_21_name">
<text>Box in the kitchen</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_21_descr">
<text>Postponed for the dealer ordering in the blue box in the summer kitchen.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_24_name">
 <text>Cache log</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_24_descr">
<text>Before going to another part of the Marshes had to unload the backpack. Part of the swag stuffed into a log.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_23_name">
<text>Stash in the switchboard</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_23_descr">
<text>Shield the transformer box on the farm. Who is a stranger fly - kill.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_25_name">
<text>electrical panel at ATP</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_25_descr">
 <text>As entered to the Grey, its the small things on the safe side have tatusova on ATP in the electrical panel. Who knows, maybe another will fit.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_26_name">
<text>Backpack on the trail</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_26_descr">
<text>On the trail of the flesh met and weapons one knife was. Backpack threw out there, you want to have a free hand and foot running was easier. It is necessary as-thread to return.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_27_name">
<text>tree Stump</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_27_descr">
 <text>Let fools share the Hook to pay. I'm going to put under the stump of a young tree.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_28_name">
<text>safe for deadwood</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_28_descr">
<text>the little Boy on drugs will delay the hiding place: behind a tree. As there will be enough rush to the mainland.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_29_name">
<text>Stash in the bushes</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_29_descr">
 <text>out Of the swamp emerged, had not the strength to go, so all I wear right next to the path amongst the bushes thrown.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_30_name">
<text>Stash under the body</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_30_descr">
<text>Under the body of KAMAZ in front of the bridge in the box of tools.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_31_name">
<text>in the Middle of the swamps</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_31_descr">
<text>in a swamp on a concrete garbage pieces of rebar left a box of stuff to ground out.</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_mar_treasure_32_name">
<text>Box in the oven</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_32_descr">
<text>the Cache, as the wizard in a fairy tale: in a casket, the casket in a furnace, the furnace in the burnt house, and the house on the Moor.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_33_name">
<text>safe in reeds</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_33_descr">
<text>I don't know where in the swamp this safe came from, but it was a sin not to take advantage. Until then may all my there lie down.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_34_name">
<text>the Swamp stump</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_mar_treasure_34_descr">
<text>Senior said, a lot of stuff not to take, so I hid it in a stump near the water pumping station there in the bushes, under the tree.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_35_name">
<text>Snag in the Marshes</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_35_descr">
<text>Walked through the Swamp, noticed near the jetty rotten snag. The place is nice, so I go here stuffed back his treasures.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_36_name">
<text>Backpack on the island</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_36_descr">
 <text>Drove me swamp thing a few kilometers, because on some island decided from a backpack to get rid of, but it would have died from such a marathon.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_37_name">
<text>the Hatch near the station</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_37_descr">
<text>Under some hatch near the station buried welcome to my random robbers got nothing.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_38_name">
<text>a Cache in the pipe</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_38_descr">
 <text>Black backpack in a large tube, the whole memory about Mitka.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_39_name">
<text>travelling Bag in the cab</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_39_descr">
<text>Found the sakvoyazhika in the swamp, put their belongings and stashed in the cab of the crane until better times.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_40_name">
<text>Backpack under the car</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_40_descr">
<text>to run it easier, left wear under the car on the railroad tracks.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_41_name">
 <text>On the cornice of the dome</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_41_descr">
<text>On the cornice of the dome-here stuffed your backpack. Rode on the top of your mountain goat!</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_42_name">
<text>Under the bridge</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_42_descr">
<text>Under the bridge sat, waiting, while chasing the top runners. There is a backpack with habarka and left - to beam some perched.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_43_name">
<text>Among the boulders</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_43_descr">
 <text>Between three boulders thrown into the gap diaper bag in order to kids not to be scorched.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_44_name">
<text>Log under boulders</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_treasure_44_descr">
<text>Long searched for a safe place for your stash, found in the reeds under the boulders snag with a hollow.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_11_name">
<text>the cache in the tomb of the</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_11_descr">
<text>Under cross buried their possessions for the time being: let the dead Stalker pooranee, he does not take per cent.</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_mil_treasure_12_name">
<text>Cross the tree</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_12_descr">
<text>Made a hiding place in the grave near the tree</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_1_name">
<text>the Case in the oven</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_1_descr">
<text>In a furnace of the ruined hut was attached to the box of swag. In the course I will be there pulling off his clothes.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_13_name">
<text>Pipe at the entrance to the base</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_13_descr">
 <text>Hid things under the nose of the ensign: in the pipe behind the guardroom at the entrance to the base.</text>
</string>
	<string id="st_mil_treasure_2_name">
<text>Backpack near the pipe</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_14_name">
<text>Stash in the "Moskvich"</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_14_descr">
<text>Max gets back, give him his backpack. Yet let ' em in the old "Moskvich".</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_2_descr">
<text>On the roof of a collapsed house near the chimney threw down his backpack. Because of the drinkers in the village to come back as something dumb...</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_3_name">
<text>Backpack under the trailer</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_mil_treasure_4_name">
<text>Stash under the bridge</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_4_descr">
<text>Backpack on the train under the bridge at the military base.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_5_name">
<text>the Cleft in the tunnel</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_5_descr">
<text>Drop your backpack in a crevice above the tunnel, when the "Frying" it worked, and he was there he hooked rebar. Sorry to leave, it will be necessary to return.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_6_name">
<text>Stash in the toilet</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_mil_treasure_6_descr">
<text>Hardly anyone will think that the cache in the village latrine to hide, so I'm almost calm.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_7_name">
<text>a Cache at the fence</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_7_descr">
<text>Behind the hangar threw backpack Kohl: was unbearable on so much just to shove!</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_8_name">
<text>Backpack under a tree</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_8_descr">
 <text>I saw the monster near the water tower, threw the backpack under a fallen tree and ran off to his light.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_15_name">
<text>Backpack in the basement</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_15_descr">
<text>After the release so sausage that was thrown in the basement of your backpack. Get up on your feet, return to the village and get them.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_16_name">
<text>backpack Forgotten</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_16_descr">
 <text>the Explosion a piece of the wall smashed, my plate was crushed. Had to remove the backpack to get out and this shit on the tomatoes slapped. A backpack and has remained there since.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_17_name">
<text>Caches in the kitchen</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_17_descr">
<text>Green backpack in the kitchen oven of one of the houses of an abandoned village. Write down the coordinates.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_18_name">
<text>Stash under a boulder</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_18_descr">
 <text>Went on the chase, between boulders in the bushes threw a backpack with stolen swag.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_3_descr">
<text>Saw a handsome man before discharge threw some backpack under the trailer. Sometime to come back, see what's there.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_9_name">
<text>the Cracked beam</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_19_name">
<text>Stash in the wood-sledge</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_19_descr">
<text>Stash in a large log near the wood-sledge</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_20_name">
 <text>Log under boulders</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_20_descr">
<text>At the edge of the boulders lies a log, and in it my caches from zaviduschie eyes.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_9_descr">
<text>Stash made in a log under a pine tree near Poblenou tower.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_10_name">
<text>tree Stump for plates</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_21_name">
<text>tree Stump near the fence</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_21_descr">
 <text>vityok said he left my share in the hollow of the stump between the fence of the military base and marsh.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_treasure_10_descr">
<text>tree Stump between two boulders behind a pile of concrete slabs</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_2_name">
<text>Blue box</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_2_descr">
<text>On the second floor of the building near the marque's got a blue box with the swag.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_1_name">
<text>Pipe in truck</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_1_descr">
 <text>Tatusova stuff in the pipe and threw in a rusty trolley in the old quarry.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_8_name">
<text>Black backpack</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_9_name">
<text>Backpack on the branch</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_9_descr">
<text>Hiding from some creature in the tree. Monstryatinu itself not seen, only heard in the fog. There threw the backpack on the branch, and he jumped - and ran there!</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_8_descr">
 <text>Damn, lost a black backpack, as he flee from the forest! Even know where, only the second time hell turn up there, except after the forest with Napalm burns.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_10_name">
<text>Wood fence</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_10_descr">
<text>To the fence of the reserve bloodsucker chasing you, bastard! Drove me up a tree. If the backpack is there left, hell to the fence took the leap.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_19_name">
<text>Backpack in the cave</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_19_descr">
 <text>Climbed at night in a cave, fell asleep. And I woke up, next thing some sort of sleeping sack my dream chews. I pulled out as a champion runner! A backpack in the cave and left.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_11_name">
<text>a Boulder near ravine</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_11_descr">
<text>the Dogs to the ravine pressed, behind the boulders threw the backpack and went for a breakthrough.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_3_name">
<text>Backpack in the bushes</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_12_name">
<text>Backpack in the woods</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_red_treasure_12_descr">
<text>Like in a horror movie visited - I don't know how got out. Lost the backpack. Theoretically "to spread" I could only be in one place.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_13_name">
<text>Backpack under boulders</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_13_descr">
<text>Before going to the bridge to Limansk under the boulders threw the backpack Kolchin he once was. This is in order, then, to go further easier.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_14_name">
<text>Damn swag</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_14_descr">
 <text>A history with this backpack: all whose it was, died. I threw away from sin, that my eyes have not seen him.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_15_name">
<text>Strange</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_15_descr">
<text>went to Sleep the night under a boulder on the backpack, and I woke up in a different place. Tried to understand, but all the time walked in a circle.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_16_name">
<text>Backpack under the collapse</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_16_descr">
 <text>At the exit of the forest Red boulders of the ravine fell, and at me! And behind them, something dark turned to me. I barely escaped, but lost your backpack in there somewhere.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_3_descr">
<text>made their Way through the bushes, dropped them in his backpack.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_17_name">
<text>John DOE</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_17_descr">
<text>Abrash, a moron, sowed my backpack among the rocks somewhere here at this point. And to come back for him chickening out, freak. Ah Yes, friend!</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_red_treasure_18_name">
<text>Stash in the tunnel</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_18_descr">
<text>an abandoned tunnel, at the end, I hid the swag.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_24_name">
<text>tree Stump in the wilderness</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_24_descr">
<text>get Lost in the Red forest and threw all my stuff into the hollow of the stump at this point.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_4_name">
<text>Things in the hollow of a tree</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_4_descr">
 <text>the road to Limansk stashed your stuff with a Whip in the hollow of a fallen tree at the exit of the reserve.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_5_name">
<text>Holey tree stump</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_6_name">
<text>tree Stump in front of the forest</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_6_descr">
<text>who knows what in these woods waiting for us, so I'm reloading in a rotten tree stump was hidden.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_7_name">
<text>tree Stump near ravine</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_7_descr">
 <text>Nedalechko from the fucking anomaly in the stump was sathariel odds and ends. Themselves wait getting this crap get to explore near this in lyubasu valuable arts should lie.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_20_name">
<text>tree stump</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_20_descr">
<text>Seva said, a big empty stump in the Red forest. On his tip-will try to find.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_21_name">
<text>Stash in a tree stump</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_21_descr">
<text>Primaily housing with all small things in the stump in the Red forest.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_22_name">
<text>tree Stump near ravine</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_22_descr">
<text>Falling off a cliff, Sudanese about this stump. It's big, so I stashed the swag</text>
</string>
	<string id="st_red_treasure_5_descr">
<text>I Heard some screeching and howling, ran off in the woods, and things vtulit in holey tree stump.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_23_name">
<text>a lock on the marque</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_treasure_23_descr">
<text>Near the descent into the mine under the seat "latch" laid down their findings. Before going to Sidorovich will shake out in the big backpack.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_15_name">
<text>safe at the farm</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yantar_treasure_15_name">
<text>Log behind garages</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_yantar_treasure_15_descr">
<text>Near the garages at the plant on Amber hid in the beam of Chabarok: the best places not found</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_22_name">
<text>a Cache under a young tree</text>
</string>
<string id="st_dark_valley_treasure_22_descr">
<text>not Far from the swamp, pipes, threw the backpack under a young tree.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_weapon_prisoner_descr">
<text>In concrete pipe hidden small safe. It some reserves for a rainy day.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_weapon_prisoner_name">
 <text>Stash major Khaletskiy</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_quest_bandit_base_name">
<text>the Old cache</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_quest_bandit_base_descr">
<text>a Cache, in which the diggers were once stored their loot.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_quest_old_pda_name">
<text>Toolbox</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_quest_old_pda_descr">
<text>the Old CCP lies under the false bottom in the box of tools</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_quest_reward_in_anomaly_name">
 <text>Stash in the anomaly</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_quest_reward_in_anomaly_descr">
<text>If you believe Yoga, in hiding among the anomalies is some sort of special gun.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_quest_smuggler_weapons_name">
<text>Boot</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_treasure_quest_smuggler_weapons_descr">
<text>According to the shopping Bags in the trunk of an old car is a consignment of goods belonging to some smuggler.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_treasure_17_descr">
 <text>On the basis of the neutrals on the Cordon ZIL keeps his junk in the box</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_10_name">
<text>a cache in the Swamps</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_10_descr">
<text>At the recycling plant in the Marshes in the funnel is a very valuable caches. What's in it is yours now.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_11_name">
<text>a box with a reward</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_11_descr">
<text>Those keys, man, you will open the safe. And there, according to my information, there is something of value.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_12_name">
<text>Reward</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_12_descr">
<text>For your money - our stash! Give guts Shh! - you're the only one.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_13_name">
<text>Suitcase</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_13_descr">
<text>if that's the case, keep the coordinates the case with the swag. Behind a dumpster near the wall find.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_14_name">
<text>safe under the bridge</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_14_descr">
<text>won't you too much shipping stories. The hiding place will find in the safe under the bridge.</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_mar_q_n_6_name">
<text>Backpack in the payment of the</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_6_descr">
<text>the Contents of the backpack, I now fill the coordinates to your PDA, compensates your financial investment in my pocket.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_7_name">
<text>Code box</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_7_descr">
<text>This fee is worthy of the swag hidden in a safe in the Swamps.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_8_name">
<text>swag as payment</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_8_descr">
 <text>Khabar will find in a black backpack under the boulders, he is now yours.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_9_name">
<text>Box at the tower</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_n_9_descr">
<text>Tell me one reliable source about swag unattended in the cache, hidden under a tower.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_a_15_name">
<text>Backpack of a dead soldier</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_a_15_descr">
<text>Get even a little more than I paid for it. Your reward in a backpack near the body of the military.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_a_3_name">
 <text>Additional efforts</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_a_3_descr">
<text>a bit More tensed and in the backpack of the dead warriors will receive product for your money, even with interest. </text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_l_16_name">
<text>not an Easy award</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_l_16_descr">
<text>'ll Reward you with information about valuable, but difficult in procuring swag. Be careful: he is the former owner of my tips proschelkal beak.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_l_1_name">
<text>Backpack on the corpse</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_l_1_descr">
 <text>Get a tip on the secret stash! It's in the backpack, and the backpack on the back of the corpse.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_l_2_name">
<text>Skydiver</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_l_2_descr">
<text>Find "grouse" on these coordinates: from his backpack and take what's coming to you.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_l_4_name">
<text>the Corpse of a soldier</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_l_4_descr">
<text>My information was this: a young soldier silently guards you in the bushes backpack.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_l_5_name">
 <text>Backpack under the pipeline</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mar_q_t_l_5_descr">
<text>Here, get coordinates on a backpack, next to the corpse of a Stalker under the pipeline lies.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q10_n_name">
<text>Stump barbed wire</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q10_n_descr">
<text>Guy, its well-deserved get in the stump near the thorns.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q1_n_name">
<text>Green box</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q1_n_descr">
 <text>Especially for you have saved swag in a green army box on the edge of the Cordon. Mind you, from my heart rip!</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q2_n_name">
<text>Backpack in the suburbs</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q2_n_descr">
<text>well, your bounties give you a stash with my shoulder, ha ha! Well, of course, and all its contents, too, can use it.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q3_t_l_name">
<text>the Road to the Swamps</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q3_t_l_descr">
<text>our Money - caches your. You will find on the way to the Swamp next to the corpse.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q4_t_a_name">
<text>the Reward for the hero</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q4_t_a_descr">
<text>Buying waiting for you in the form of a backpack next to the corpse of a hapless Stalker. Landmark - near old locomotive.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q5_n_name">
<text>Reward</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q5_n_descr">
<text>you will Find the geocache on my GPS under a tree in the backpack.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q6_n_name">
<text>Go - do not kill</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q6_n_descr">
 <text>My part of the deal - in the switchboard of the Elevator. Go to it quietly, if anomaly there. And electricity and so is long over.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q7_n_name">
<text>Case under train car</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q7_n_descr">
<text>Your a catch - the contents of the briefcase under the car on the railroad.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q8_n_name">
<text>About the tomb</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q8_n_descr">
<text>it is Wrong to dig up graves. However, my stash is hidden in a fake mound, so the dead don't disturb anyone.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q9_t_a_name">
<text>the Case for landfill</text>
</string>
<string id="st_esc_q9_t_a_descr">
<text>I'll Pay you the contents of the briefcase that was lying next to an anomaly behind the junkyard at the Cordon. There Adam another friend takes to him, so don't worry, he is not a fighter.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q10_n_name">
<text>tree Stump on the edge of the Landfill</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q10_n_descr">
<text>well, share naladochnoe on a stash of swag: look in the stump on the edge of the Dump, everything is yours.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q1_n_name">
 <text>Black backpack in wreckage</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q1_n_descr">
<text>what you now owe, you will find in a black backpack in the wreckage of a construction crane.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q2_n_name">
<text>Scrap pipe</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q2_n_descr">
<text>I the money was received, and you will have your drygalskii to datapath to the cache pruning of the pipe.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q3_n_name">
<text>Box the fuse box is in the ruins</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q3_n_descr">
 <text>Oh, for yourself once the stash is organized... Yes, that really now, you have to take it.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q4_n_name">
<text>Box in the radiation garbage</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q4_n_descr">
<text>you Offer the coordinates for the box of swag. Most importantly, her eggs there not fry background rolls. </text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q5_n_name">
<text>Box in the clutches of the bulldozer</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q5_n_descr">
<text>At the base of the feet dozer will find what bought.</text>
</string>
	<string id="st_gar_q6_t_l_name">
<text>dead man's Backpack</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q6_t_l_descr">
<text>the Ghosts are not afraid? Then look for a stash in the backpack next to the dead man.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q7_t_l_name">
<text>the body of the excavator</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q7_t_l_descr">
<text>the inverted excavator one good-natured kid with you to pay off the contents of his backpack.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q8_t_a_name">
<text>Corpse in the Dustbin</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q8_t_a_descr">
 <text>you'll Have to work hard to pick up due! Take the swag out of my backpack killed by the anomaly.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q9_n_name">
<text>on the way to Agroprom</text>
</string>
<string id="st_gar_q9_n_descr">
<text>In the UAZ on the way to Agroprom look for a box that small. I think you will not be offended.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q10_n_name">
<text>safe in the hangar</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q10_n_descr">
<text>I kept my word. The promise of nychka's waiting for you in the safe at the old factory.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q11_t_l_name">
 <text>the Corpse of the stones</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q11_t_l_descr">
<text>backpack near where the body of the stones will find what you pay go.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q1_n_name">
<text>the tank</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q1_n_descr">
<text>backpack under the tank take my swag - it's yours.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q2_n_name">
<text>the Bush from ate</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q2_n_descr">
<text>I Hid once with a good salable swag in the Bush. Now here was useful, so that you to pay.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q3_t_a_name">
<text>the Corpse of a soldier</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q3_t_a_descr">
<text>Record of the old securities habare what's in the backpack the unfortunate Solda is stored. It's right next to the anomaly.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q4_n_name">
<text>swag in the bushes</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q4_n_descr">
<text>I always pay my bills, so here, take the coordinates of the swag.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q5_n_name">
<text>safe on base "Liberty"</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q5_n_descr">
 <text>In treatice on the basis of "Freedom" in the safe something waiting for finder good Khabarov.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q6_n_name">
<text>Box in the tower</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q6_n_descr">
<text>I Appreciate your interest! As a reward for it get the contents of the blue box on the tower for the base of "Freedom".</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q7_n_name">
<text>Stalker tomb</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q7_n_descr">
<text>Your Board is under the Stalker cross the grave by the old tree.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q8_n_name">
 <text>Drawer under seat</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q8_n_descr">
<text>Under the driver's seat of a red LAZ will find a box. And what is in it, you're on your own.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q9_n_name">
<text>tree Stump near the fence</text>
</string>
<string id="st_val_q9_n_descr">
<text>For such cases stashed my stuff in a stump near the fence.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q10_t_l_name">
<text>Confiscated from the anomaly</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q10_t_l_descr">
 <text>the soldier Stepped into the anomaly, and a backpack with swag that stalkers chop off, and left to lie down next to. If you're lucky, so will be able to get hold of.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q1_n_name">
<text>Under a fence from a barbed wire</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q1_n_descr">
<text>So in payment I'll give you a secret cache at the fence in the Stalker backpack. Focus on high-voltage tower.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q2_n_name">
<text>Under vyvoroten</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q2_n_descr">
 <text>Camera store in the Area no, sorry. If you hurry, you will find the caches under fallen tree, in the backpack.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q3_t_a_name">
<text>Corpse in the hearth of radiation</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q3_t_a_descr">
<text>I Want a noble geocaching? They have me. Get if not afraid of using a source of radiation turn up. There right next to the corpse of your prize and lies.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q4_n_name">
<text>the tanks at the tomb of the</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q4_n_descr">
 <text>a deal's a Deal! You will find the cache in the cylinders on the tomb of the unknown.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q5_n_name">
<text>Corner</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q5_n_descr">
<text>On the corner of the fence in the old stump something since the last release of stashed Kolka Scythe... God rest his soul.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q6_n_name">
<text>switchboard</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q6_n_descr">
<text>my Stash... well, now it is yours so it is in the fuse-box on the basis of "Debt".</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q7_n_name">
 <text>the Deck near the tree</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q7_n_descr">
<text>Good people told me here the other day about a cache of our enemies. Scoop some out if you please!</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q8_t_a_name">
<text>Corpse in the van</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q8_t_a_descr">
<text>Warriors drove his bus that flew into the anomaly and crashed here in this square. Their whole swag is yours now.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q9_n_name">
<text>safe under the landslide</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agr_q9_n_descr">
 <text>Under the ravine to bury the safe with the good. We assume, for you as for friend tried.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_q1_n_name">
<text>Cross under stairs</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_q1_n_descr">
<text>In the first place stash! But you can be sure that nobody looted. In the subway under the staircase look.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_q2_n_name">
<text>the Case in dungeons</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_q2_n_descr">
<text>At the bottom of the spiral staircase, if you do not disturb the inhabitants of the subway, find the lost case with the good.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_q3_t_a_name">
<text>subway</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_q3_t_a_descr">
<text>Here is the place where pick up the military backpack that the subway of the Agricultural industry fell into the anomaly. Myself, don't get into any trouble!</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_q4_n_name">
<text>Pipe in the collector</text>
</string>
<string id="st_agru_q4_n_descr">
<text>Know the records in PDA stalkers that the subway NII Agroprom stash the swag. To rewrite the coordinates. </text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q8_t_l_name">
<text>Corpse in the lake</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_yan_q8_t_l_descr">
<text>you Search the backpack of a dead soldier that the lapping lake.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q1_n_name">
<text>Crate on the roof of the boiler room</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q1_n_descr">
<text>There is one hiding spot on the roof of the boiler room in the blue box. Near the zombie swarm, so be careful.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q2_n_name">
<text>Box in the car</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q2_n_descr">
<text>Everything is fine! Here, instead of the coordinates of the box inside the car at the factory. All will understand.</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_yan_q3_t_l_name">
<text>backpack on the sewer</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q3_t_l_descr">
<text>you will Find the backpack at the sewer - and we're even. Near the body lies, so to calculate easily.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q4_n_name">
<text>the Case on a scientific basis</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q4_n_descr">
<text>Excellent! Take everything you find inside the box in the trunk of a UAZ on a scientific basis.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q5_n_name">
<text>Box electrical</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q5_n_descr">
 <text>the money For your answer by the coordinates of the caches in the booth near the plant.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q6_n_name">
<text>the Bell of the tank</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q6_n_descr">
<text>the bell of the bottom of the tank at the factory stashed something. What - do not know, did not check.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q7_n_name">
<text>the cabin of the MAZ</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q7_n_descr">
<text>odds and ends will find in the cabin of the MAZ, it is in case of Packed.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_yan_q9_n_name">
<text>tree Stump in front of the camp of the scientists</text>
</string>
 <string id="st_yan_q9_n_descr">
<text>Look for the stash under the stump opposite the base scientists.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q10_n_name">
<text>Pipe in the mine</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q10_n_descr">
<text>know that something valuable is in this stash in the Red forest.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q1_t_l_name">
<text>Dead Stalker</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q1_t_l_descr">
<text>the PDA of the dead Stalker found out that in his backpack was something interesting. Coordinates take off you.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q2_t_a_name">
 <text>a Dangerous hiding place</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q2_t_a_descr">
<text>Already gave one shot about the old stash, but I do know that this sucker so it never took - the anomaly nearby bent.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q3_n_name">
<text>Red gate</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q3_n_descr">
<text>the Cache is hidden behind the red valve in the piping at the mine. There - dunno, I'm not interested.</text>
</string>
	<string id="st_red_q4_n_name">
<text>Bus</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q4_n_descr">
<text>Under the back seat of the bus, a friend made a hiding place. A friend now living there, so he will not be offended.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q5_n_name">
<text>Pipe in rubble</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q5_n_descr">
<text>found Out about this hidden from the prisoner. In General, it is in the pile behind the APC in the pipe segment.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q6_n_name">
<text>a Box with a backpack</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q6_n_descr">
 <text>Treasure your downright fabulous! Remember: the reward is in the backpack, the backpack in the bin, at the bridge, and the bridge in Red forest.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q7_t_a_name">
<text>the poor man's Backpack</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q7_t_a_descr">
<text>One poor old backpack I was carrying, only through the Red forest and did not pass. In General, if you will, all thy will.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q8_n_name">
<text>safe at trolley</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q8_n_descr">
<text>No shit, in the safe at the overturned trolleys buried one a tramp, something valuable!</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q9_n_name">
<text>plain old tree stump</text>
</string>
<string id="st_red_q9_n_descr">
<text>stash in hollowed-out tree stump. The place is inconspicuous without coordinates Fig find. Now I'm with salt...</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q10_n_name">
<text>Stash in the woods</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q10_n_descr">
<text>Stash under rocks in the forest backpack. Catch position is... in good hands why not give it?</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q1_t_l_name">
<text>Backpack under the body</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q1_t_l_descr">
 <text>the Cache is not the cache, only valuable swag in that bag on the water tower needs to be.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q2_n_name">
<text>the Caches under vyvoroten</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q2_n_descr">
<text>Pass from the hands of the old caches under fallen tree.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q3_n_name">
<text>grandma's safety Deposit box</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q3_n_descr">
<text>Where the stove came from the box - don't know, but have information that it is not empty there.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q4_n_name">
 <text>Sepulchral stash</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q4_n_descr">
<text>There is information that you can get rich, digging beneath the cross here at these coordinates.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q5_n_name">
<text>Crate on an army base</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q5_n_descr">
<text>If you can get on the army base, you will find it in one of the attics of the box with the reward for your efforts.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q6_n_a_name">
<text>safe in the closet</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q6_n_a_descr">
 <text>Have any information about that in the safe in the barracks, the warriors kept something.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q7_n_a_name">
<text>Small box</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q7_n_a_descr">
<text>Captain Eltishev all this box was running, is it in another square not moved. You will find - I will look that there is standing.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q8_n_a_name">
<text>the Mountain of garbage</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q8_n_a_descr">
<text>Java specifically hiding in the garbage was satarel, only he forgot about it. But I'm still clearly recorded! Now give you.</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q9_n_a_name">
<text>a Box with a secret</text>
</string>
<string id="st_mil_q9_n_a_descr">
<text>Behind the cabin of the army MAZ have the box, but not simple, with a secret. Here's the secret and sell.</text>
</string>
</string_table>
